{
  "title": "AZ-900 Azure Fundamentals",
  "description": "Microsoft Azure Fundamentals - 459 Questions",
  "totalQuestions": 459,
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "original_number": "1",
      "question": "Your company intends to subscribe to an Azure support plan.\nThe support plan must allow for new support requests to be opened.\nWhich of the following are support plans that will allow this? Answer by dragging the correct option from the list to the answer area.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/support/plans/",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "original_number": "2",
      "question": "Your company has datacenters in Los Angeles and New York. The company has a Microsoft Azure subscription.\nYou are con+guring the two datacenters as geo-clustered sites for site resiliency.\nYou need to recommend an Azure storage redundancy option.\nYou have the following data storage requirements:\n✑ Data must be stored on multiple nodes.\n✑ Data must be stored on nodes in separate geographic locations.\n✑ Data can be read from the secondary location as well as from the primary location\nWhich of the following Azure stored redundancy options should you recommend?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Geo-redundant storage"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Read-only geo-redundant storage"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Zone-redundant storage"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Locally redundant storage"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/storage/common/storage-redundancy https://docs.microsoft.com/en-\nus/azure/storage/common/storage-redundancy-grs#read-access-geo-redundant-storage",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "original_number": "3",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYour company's Azure subscription includes a Basic support plan.\nThey would like to request an assessment of an Azure environment's design from Microsoft. This is, however, not supported by the existing plan.\nYou want to make sure that the company subscribes to a support plan that allows this functionality, while keeping expenses to a minimum.\nSolution: You recommend that the company subscribes to the Professional Direct support plan.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nR",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/support/plans/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "original_number": "4",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYou are tasked with deploying Azure virtual machines for your company.\nYou need to make use of the appropriate cloud deployment solution.\nSolution: You should make use of Software as a Service (SaaS).\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "original_number": "5",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYou are tasked with deploying Azure virtual machines for your company.\nYou need to make use of the appropriate cloud deployment solution.\nSolution: You should make use of Platform as a Service (PaaS).\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "original_number": "6",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYou are tasked with deploying Azure virtual machines for your company.\nYou need to make use of the appropriate cloud deployment solution.\nSolution: You should make use of Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS).\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "original_number": "7",
      "question": "Your developers have created 10 web applications that must be host on Azure.\nYou need to determine which Azure web tier plan to host the web apps. The web tier plan must meet the following requirements:\n✑ The web apps will use custom domains.\n✑ The web apps each require 10 GB of storage.\n✑ The web apps must each run in dedicated compute instances.\n✑ Load balancing between instances must be included.\n✑ Costs must be minimized.\nWhich web tier plan should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Standard"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Basic"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Free"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Shared"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nS",
      "explanation": "http://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/pricing/details/websites/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "original_number": "8",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYou are planning to migrate a company to Azure. Each of the company's numerous divisions will have an administrator in place to manage the\nAzure resources used by their respective division.\nYou want to make sure that the Azure deployment you employ allows for Azure to be segmented for the divisions, while keeping administrative\neffort to a minimum.\nSolution: You plan to make use of several Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) directories.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "original_number": "9",
      "question": "Your developers have created a portal web app for users in the Miami branch ohce. The web app will be publicly accessible and used by the\nMiami users to retrieve customer and product information. The web app is currently running in an on-premises test environment.\nYou plan to host the web app on Azure.\nYou need to determine which Azure web tier plan to host the web app. The web tier plan must meet the following requirements:\n✑ The website will use the miami.weyland.com URL.\n✑ The website will be deployed to two instances.\n✑ SSL support must be included.\n✑ The website requires 12 GB of storage.\n✑ Costs must be minimized.\nWhich web tier plan should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Standard"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Basic"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Free"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Shared"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nR",
      "explanation": "http://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/documentation/articles/azure-subscription-service-limits/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "original_number": "10",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYour company is planning to migrate all their virtual machines to an Azure pay-as-you-go subscription. The virtual machines are currently hosted\non the Hyper-V hosts in a data center.\nYou are required make sure that the intended Azure solution uses the correct expenditure model.\nSolution: You should recommend the use of the elastic expenditure model.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "original_number": "11",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYour company is planning to migrate all their virtual machines to an Azure pay-as-you-go subscription. The virtual machines are currently hosted\non the Hyper-V hosts in a data center.\nYou are required make sure that the intended Azure solution uses the correct expenditure model.\nSolution: You should recommend the use of the scalable expenditure model.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "original_number": "12",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYour company is planning to migrate all their virtual machines to an Azure pay-as-you-go subscription. The virtual machines are currently hosted\non the Hyper-V hosts in a data center.\nYou are required make sure that the intended Azure solution uses the correct expenditure model.\nSolution: You should recommend the use of the operational expenditure model.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "original_number": "13",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYou are required to deploy an Arti+cial Intelligence (AI) solution in Azure.\nYou want to make sure that you are able to build, test, and deploy predictive analytics for the solution.\nSolution: You should make use of Azure Cosmos DB.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "original_number": "14",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYour company's Active Directory forest includes thousands of user accounts.\nYou have been informed that all network resources will be migrated to Azure. Thereafter, the on-premises data center will be retired.\nYou are required to employ a strategy that reduces the effect on users, once the planned migration has been completed.\nSolution: You plan to sync all the Active Directory user accounts to Azure Active Directory (Azure AD).\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "original_number": "15",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYou are required to deploy an Arti+cial Intelligence (AI) solution in Azure.\nYou want to make sure that you are able to build, test, and deploy predictive analytics for the solution.\nSolution: You should make use of Azure Machine Learning Studio.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "original_number": "16",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYour company's infrastructure includes a number of business units that each need a large number of various Azure resources for everyday\noperation.\nThe resources required by each business unit are identical.\nYou are required to sanction a strategy to create Azure resources automatically.\nSolution: You recommend that the Azure API Management service be included in the strategy.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "original_number": "17",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYour company's infrastructure includes a number of business units that each need a large number of various Azure resources for everyday\noperation.\nThe resources required by each business unit are identical.\nYou are required to sanction a strategy to create Azure resources automatically.\nSolution: You recommend that management groups be included in the strategy.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "original_number": "18",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYour company's infrastructure includes a number of business units that each need a large number of various Azure resources for everyday\noperation.\nThe resources required by each business unit are identical.\nYou are required to sanction a strategy to create Azure resources automatically.\nSolution: You recommend that the Azure Resource Manager templates be included in the strategy.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "original_number": "19",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYou are tasked with deploying a critical LOB application, which will be installed on a virtual machine, to Azure.\nYou are informed that the application deployment strategy should allow for a guaranteed availability of 99.99 percent. You need to make sure that\nthe strategy requires as little virtual machines and availability zones as possible.\nSolution: You include two virtual machines and one availability zone in your strategy.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nR",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/availability-zones/az-overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "original_number": "20",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYou are tasked with deploying a critical LOB application, which will be installed on a virtual machine, to Azure.\nYou are informed that the application deployment strategy should allow for a guaranteed availability of 99.99 percent. You need to make sure that\nthe strategy requires as little virtual machines and availability zones as possible.\nSolution: You include one virtual machine and two availability zones in your strategy.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nR",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/availability-zones/az-overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "original_number": "21",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYou are tasked with deploying a critical LOB application, which will be installed on a virtual machine, to Azure.\nYou are informed that the application deployment strategy should allow for a guaranteed availability of 99.99 percent. You need to make sure that\nthe strategy requires as little virtual machines and availability zones as possible.\nSolution: You include two virtual machines and two availability zones in your strategy.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nR",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/availability-zones/az-overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "original_number": "22",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYour company's developers intend to deploy a large number of custom virtual machines on a weekly basis. They will also be removing these\nvirtual machines during the same week it was deployed. Sixty percent of the virtual machines have Windows Server 2016 installed, while the other\nforty percent has Ubuntu Linux installed.\nYou are required to make sure that the administrative effort, needed for this process, is reduced by employing a suitable Azure service.\nSolution: You recommend the use of Microsoft Managed Desktop.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "original_number": "23",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYour company's developers intend to deploy a large number of custom virtual machines on a weekly basis. They will also be removing these\nvirtual machines during the same week it was deployed. Sixty percent of the virtual machines have Windows Server 2016 installed, while the other\nforty percent has Ubuntu Linux installed.\nYou are required to make sure that the administrative effort, needed for this process, is reduced by employing a suitable Azure service.\nSolution: You recommend the use of Azure Reserved Virtual Machines (VM) Instances.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "original_number": "24",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYour company's developers intend to deploy a large number of custom virtual machines on a weekly basis. They will also be removing these\nvirtual machines during the same week it was deployed. Sixty percent of the virtual machines have Windows Server 2016 installed, while the other\nforty percent has Ubuntu Linux installed.\nYou are required to make sure that the administrative effort, needed for this process, is reduced by employing a suitable Azure service.\nSolution: You recommend the use of Azure DevTest Labs.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "original_number": "25",
      "question": "Your company has virtual machines (VMs) hosted in Microsoft Azure. The VMs are located in a single Azure virtual network named VNet1.\nThe company has users that work remotely. The remote workers require access to the VMs on VNet1.\nYou need to provide access for the remote workers.\nWhat should you do?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Con+gure a Site-to-Site (S2S) VPN."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Con+gure a VNet-toVNet VPN."
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Con+gure a Point-to-Site (P2S) VPN."
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Con+gure DirectAccess on a Windows Server 2012 server VM."
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "Con+gure a Multi-Site VPN"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nA P",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/vpn-gateway/vpn-gateway-about-vpngateways",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "original_number": "26",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYou have been informed by your superiors of the company's intentions to automate server deployment to Azure. There is, however, some concern\nthat administrative credentials could be uncovered during this process.\nYou are required to make sure that during the deployment, the administrative credentials are encrypted using a suitable Azure solution.\nSolution: You recommend the use of Azure Information Protection.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "original_number": "27",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYou have been informed by your superiors of the company's intentions to automate server deployment to Azure. There is, however, some concern\nthat administrative credentials could be uncovered during this process.\nYou are required to make sure that during the deployment, the administrative credentials are encrypted using a suitable Azure solution.\nSolution: You recommend the use of Azure Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA).\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "original_number": "28",
      "question": "The company would like to develop a cloud solution by making use of Azure Government. Azure Government can only be used by certain types of\nclients to develop cloud solutions.\nWhich of the following are the types of customers that can make use of Azure Government in this situation? Answer by dragging the correct\n\noption from the list to the answer area.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/modules/intro-to-azure-government/2-what-is-azure-government",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "original_number": "29",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYour company has an Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) environment. Users occasionally connect to Azure AD via the Internet.\nYou have been tasked with making sure that users who connect to Azure AD via the internet from an unidenti+ed IP address, are automatically\nencouraged to change passwords.\nSolution: You con+gure the use of Azure AD Identity Protection.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nR",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/active-directory/identity-protection/howto-sign-in-risk-policy",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "original_number": "30",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYour company has an Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) environment. Users occasionally connect to Azure AD via the Internet.\nYou have been tasked with making sure that users who connect to Azure AD via the internet from an unidenti+ed IP address, are automatically\nencouraged to change passwords.\nSolution: You con+gure the use of Azure AD Privileged Identity Management.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nR",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/active-directory/identity-protection/howto-sign-in-risk-policy",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "original_number": "31",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYou are planning a strategy to deploy numerous web servers and database servers to Azure.\nThis strategy should allow for connection types between the web servers and database servers to be controlled.\nSolution: You include network security groups (NSGs) in your strategy.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "original_number": "32",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYou are planning a strategy to deploy numerous web servers and database servers to Azure.\nThis strategy should allow for connection types between the web servers and database servers to be controlled.\nSolution: You include a local network gateway in your strategy.\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "original_number": "33",
      "question": "Note: The question is included in a number of questions that depicts the identical set-up. However, every question has a distinctive result.\nEstablish if the solution satis+es the requirements.\nYour company's Active Directory forest includes thousands of user accounts.\nYou have been informed that all network resources will be migrated to Azure. Thereafter, the on-premises data center will be retired.\nYou are required to employ a strategy that reduces the effect on users, once the planned migration has been completed.\nSolution: You plan to require Azure Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA).\nDoes the solution meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "original_number": "34",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "Yes",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nA PaaS solution does not provide access to the operating system. The Azure Web Apps service provides an environment for you to host your\n\nweb applications.\nBehind the scenes, the web apps are hosted on virtual machines running IIS. However, you have no direct access to the virtual machine, the\noperating system or\nIIS.\nBox 2: Yes -\nA PaaS solution that hosts web apps in Azure does provide the ability to scale the platform automatically. This is known as autoscaling. Behind\nthe scenes, the web apps are hosted on virtual machines running IIS. Autoscaling means adding more load balanced virtual machines to host\nthe web apps.\nBox 3: Yes -\nPaaS provides a framework that developers can build upon to develop or customize cloud-based applications. PaaS development tools can cut\nthe time it takes to code new apps with pre-coded application components built into the platform, such as workjow, directory services, security\nfeatures, search and so on.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "A PaaS solution does not provide access to the operating system",
        "A PaaS solution that hosts web apps in Azure does provide the ability to scale the platform automatically",
        "PaaS provides a framework that developers can build upon to develop or customize cloud-based applications"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "original_number": "35",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Traditionally, IT expenses have been considered a Capital Expenditure (CapEx)",
        "Two virtual machines using the same size could have different disk con+gurations",
        "When an Azure virtual machine is stopped, you don't pay for the virtual machine"
      ],
      "answer": [
        "Yes",
        "No",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: Yes -\nTraditionally, IT expenses have been considered a Capital Expenditure (CapEx). Today, with the move to the cloud and the pay-as-you-go model,\norganizations have the ability to stretch their budgets and are shifting their IT CapEx costs to Operating Expenditures (OpEx) instead. This\njexibility, in accounting terms, is now an option due to the ג€as a Serviceג€ model of purchasing software, cloud storage and other IT related\nresources.\nBox 2: No -\nTwo virtual machines using the same size could have different disk con+gurations. Therefore, the monthly costs could be different.\nBox 3: Yes -\nWhen an Azure virtual machine is stopped, you don't pay for the virtual machine. However, you do still pay for the storage costs associated to\nthe virtual machine.\nThe most common storage costs are for the disks attached to the virtual machines. There are also other storage costs associated with a virtual\nmachine such as storage for diagnostic data and virtual machine backups."
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "original_number": "36",
      "question": "To complete the sentence, select the appropriate option in the answer area.\n\nWhen you are implementing a _______ solution, you are responsible for configuring the solution. Everything else is managed by the cloud provider.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Software as a Service (SaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Platform as a Service (PaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Serverless computing"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "When you are implementing a Software as a Service (SaaS) solution, you are responsible for configuring the SaaS solution. Everything else is managed by the cloud provider. SaaS requires the least amount of management. The cloud provider is responsible for managing everything, and the end user just uses the software.",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "original_number": "37",
      "question": "You have an on-premises network that contains several servers.\nYou plan to migrate all the servers to Azure.\nYou need to recommend a solution to ensure that some of the servers are available if a single Azure data center goes oline for an extended\nperiod.\nWhat should you include in the recommendation?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "fault tolerance"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "elasticity"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "scalability"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "low latency"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nF",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machines/windows/manage-availability",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "original_number": "38",
      "question": "To complete the sentence, select the appropriate option in the answer area.\n\nAn organization that hosts its infrastructure _______ no longer requires a data center.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "in a private cloud"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "in a hybrid cloud"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "in the public cloud"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "on a Hyper-V host"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "A private cloud is hosted in your datacenter. Therefore, you cannot close your datacenter if you are using a private cloud. A public cloud is hosted externally, for example, in Microsoft Azure. An organization that hosts its infrastructure in a public cloud can close its data center. Public cloud is the most common deployment model. In this case, you have no local hardware to manage or keep up-to-date; everything runs on your cloud provider's hardware. Microsoft Azure is an example of a public cloud provider.",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 39,
      "original_number": "39",
      "question": "What are two characteristics of the public cloud? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "dedicated hardware"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "unsecured connections"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "limited storage"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "metered pricing"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "self-service management"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "DE\nW",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-gb/learn/modules/principles-cloud-computing/4-cloud-deployment-models",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 40,
      "original_number": "40",
      "question": "When planning to migrate a public website to Azure, you must plan to _______",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "deploy a VPN"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "pay monthly usage costs"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "pay to transfer all the website data to Azure"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "reduce the number of connections to the website"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "When planning to migrate a public website to Azure, you must plan to pay monthly usage costs. This is because Azure uses the pay-as-you-go model.",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 41,
      "original_number": "41",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYour company plans to migrate all its data and resources to Azure.\nThe company's migration plan states that only Platform as a Service (PaaS) solutions must be used in Azure.\nYou need to deploy an Azure environment that meets the company migration plan.\nSolution: You create an Azure App Service and Azure SQL databases.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nA",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 42,
      "original_number": "42",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYour company plans to migrate all its data and resources to Azure.\nThe company's migration plan states that only Platform as a Service (PaaS) solutions must be used in Azure.\nYou need to deploy an Azure environment that meets the company migration plan.\nSolution: You create an Azure App Service and Azure virtual machines that have Microsoft SQL Server installed.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nA",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/overview/what-is-paas/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 43,
      "original_number": "43",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYour company plans to migrate all its data and resources to Azure.\nThe company's migration plan states that only Platform as a Service (PaaS) solutions must be used in Azure.\nYou need to deploy an Azure environment that meets the company migration plan.\nSolution: You create an Azure App Service and Azure Storage accounts.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 44,
      "original_number": "44",
      "question": "Your company hosts an accounting application named App1 that is used by all the customers of the company.\nApp1 has low usage during the +rst three weeks of each month and very high usage during the last week of each month.\nWhich bene+t of Azure Cloud Services supports cost management for this type of usage pattern?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "high availability"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "high latency"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "elasticity"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "load balancing"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nE",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/overview/what-is-elastic-computing/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 45,
      "original_number": "45",
      "question": "You plan to migrate a web application to Azure. The web application is accessed by external users.\nYou need to recommend a cloud deployment solution to minimize the amount of administrative effort used to manage the web application.\nWhat should you include in the recommendation?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Software as a Service (SaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Platform as a Service (PaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Database as a Service (DaaS)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/security/fundamentals/paas-applications-using-app-services",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 46,
      "original_number": "46",
      "question": "Which cloud deployment solution is used for Azure virtual machines and Azure SQL databases?\n\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "Yes",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Azure virtual machines are an example of Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS). Azure SQL databases are an example of Platform as a Service (PaaS).",
      "questionType": "MATCHING",
      "matchingItems": [
        {
          "item": "Azure virtual machines",
          "options": [
            "Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS)",
            "Platform as a Service (PaaS)",
            "Software as a Service (SaaS)"
          ],
          "answer": "Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS)"
        },
        {
          "item": "Azure SQL databases",
          "options": [
            "Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS)",
            "Platform as a Service (PaaS)",
            "Software as a Service (SaaS)"
          ],
          "answer": "Platform as a Service (PaaS)"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 47,
      "original_number": "47",
      "question": "You have an on-premises network that contains 100 servers.\nYou need to recommend a solution that provides additional resources to your users. The solution must minimize capital and operational\nexpenditure costs.\nWhat should you include in the recommendation?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a complete migration to the public cloud"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an additional data center"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a private cloud"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a hybrid cloud"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-gb/learn/modules/principles-cloud-computing/4-cloud-deployment-models",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 48,
      "original_number": "48",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "Yes",
        "No"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nIt is not true that a company must always migrate from a private cloud model to implement a hybrid cloud. You could start with a public cloud\nand then combine that with an on-premise infrastructure to implement a hybrid cloud.\nBox 2: Yes -\nA company can extend the capacity of its internal network by using the public cloud. This is very common. When you need more capacity, rather\nthan pay out for new on-premises infrastructure, you can con+gure a cloud environment and connect your on-premises network to the cloud\nenvironment by using a VPN.\nBox 3: No -\nIt is not true that only guest users can access cloud resources. You can give anyone with an account in Azure Active Directory access to the\ncloud resources.\nThere are many authentication scenarios but a common one is to replicate your on-premises Active Directory accounts to Azure Active\nDirectory and provide access to the Azure Active Directory accounts. Another commonly used authentication method is 'Federation' where\nauthe",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "It is not true that a company must always migrate from a private cloud model to implement a hybrid cloud",
        "A company can extend the capacity of its internal network by using the public cloud",
        "It is not true that only guest users can access cloud resources"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 49,
      "original_number": "49",
      "question": "You plan to migrate several servers from an on-premises network to Azure.\nWhat is an advantage of using a public cloud service for the servers over an on-premises network?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "The public cloud is owned by the public, NOT a private corporation"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "The public cloud is a crowd-sourcing solution that provides corporations with the ability to enhance the cloud"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "All public cloud resources can be freely accessed by every member of the public"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "The public cloud is a shared entity whereby multiple corporations each use a portion of the resources in the cloud"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nT",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 50,
      "original_number": "50",
      "question": "To complete the sentence, select the appropriate option in the answer area.\n\nAzure Site Recovery provides _______ for virtual machines.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "fault tolerance"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "disaster recovery"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "elasticity"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "high availability"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Azure Site Recovery helps ensure business continuity by keeping business apps and workloads running during outages. Site Recovery replicates workloads running on physical and virtual machines (VMs) from a primary site to a secondary location.",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 51,
      "original_number": "51",
      "question": "In which type of cloud model are all the hardware resources owned by a third-party and shared between multiple tenants?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "private"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "hybrid"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "public"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nM",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 52,
      "original_number": "52",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 53,
      "original_number": "53",
      "question": "You have 1,000 virtual machines hosted on the Hyper-V hosts in a data center.\nYou plan to migrate all the virtual machines to an Azure pay-as-you-go subscription.\nYou need to identify which expenditure model to use for the planned Azure solution.\nWhich expenditure model should you identify?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "operational"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "elastic"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "capital"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "scalable"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nO",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/architecture/cloud-adoption/appendix/azure-scaffold",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 54,
      "original_number": "54",
      "question": "Match the Azure services bene+ts to the correct descriptions.\nInstructions: To answer, drag the appropriate bene+t from the column on the left to its description on the right. Each bene+t may be used once,\nmore than once, or not at all.\nNOTE: Each correct match is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://msdn.microsoft.com/en-us/magazine/mt422582.aspx\nhttps://searchdisasterrecovery.techtarget.com/de+nition/cloud-disaster-recovery-cloud-DR http://www.siasmsp.com/the-bene+t-of-scalability-\nin-cloud-computing-2/ https://azure.microsoft.com/en-in/overview/what-is-cloud-computing/",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 55,
      "original_number": "55",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "Yes",
        "No"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nIt is not true that a company must always migrate from an internal network to implement a hybrid cloud. You could start with a public cloud and\nthen combine that with an on-premise infrastructure to implement a hybrid cloud.\nBox 2: Yes -\nA company can extend the computing resources of its internal network by using the public cloud. This is very common. When you need more\nresources, rather than pay out for new on-premises infrastructure, you can con+gure a cloud environment and connect your on-premises\nnetwork to the cloud environment by using a VPN.\nBox 3: No -\nIt is not true that only guest users can access cloud resources. You can give anyone with an account in Azure Active Directory access to the\n\ncloud resources.\nThere are many authentication scenarios but a common one is to replicate your on-premises Active Directory accounts to Azure Active\nDirectory and provide access to the Azure Active Directory accounts. Another commonly used authentication method is 'Federation' ",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "It is not true that a company must always migrate from an internal network to implement a hybrid cloud",
        "A company can extend the computing resources of its internal network by using the public cloud",
        "It is not true that only guest users can access cloud resources"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 56,
      "original_number": "56",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 57,
      "original_number": "57",
      "question": "Your company has an on-premises network that contains multiple servers.\nThe company plans to reduce the following administrative responsibilities:\n✑ Backing up application data\n✑ Replacing failed server hardware\n✑ Managing physical server security\n✑ Updating server operating systems\n✑ Managing permissions to shared documents\nThe company plans to migrate servers to Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to identify which administrative responsibilities will be eliminated after the planned migration.\nWhich two responsibilities should you identify? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Replacing failed server hardware"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Backing up application data"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Managing physical server security"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Updating server operating systems"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "Managing permissions to shared documents"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "AC\nA",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 58,
      "original_number": "58",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "No",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nWith the pay-as-go model, you pay for services as you use them. This is Opex (Operational Expenditure), not CapEx (Captial Expenditure). CapEx\nis where you pay for something upfront. For example, buying a new physical server.\nBox 2: No -\nPaying for electricity for your own datacenter will be classed as CapEx, not OpEx.\nBox 3: Yes -\nDeploying your own datacenter is an example of CapEx. This is because you need to purchase all the infrastructure upfront before you can use\nit.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "With the pay-as-go model, you pay for services as you use them",
        "Paying for electricity for your own datacenter will be classed as CapEx, not OpEx.",
        "Deploying your own datacenter is an example of CapEx"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 59,
      "original_number": "59",
      "question": "You plan to provision Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS) resources in Azure.\nWhich resource is an example of IaaS?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "an Azure web app"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an Azure virtual machine"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "an Azure logic app"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "an Azure SQL database"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nA",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/overview/what-is-iaas/\nhttps://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/overview/what-is-paas/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 60,
      "original_number": "60",
      "question": "To which cloud models can you deploy physical servers?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "private cloud and hybrid cloud only"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "private cloud only"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "private cloud, hybrid cloud and public cloud"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "hybrid cloud only"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nA",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/overview/what-is-hybrid-cloud-computing/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 61,
      "original_number": "61",
      "question": "Match the cloud model to the correct advantage.\nInstructions: To answer, drag the appropriate cloud model from the column on the left to its advantage on the right. Each cloud model may be\nused once, more than once, or not at all.\nNOTE: Each correct match is worth one point",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 62,
      "original_number": "62",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nYou cannot add physical servers to the public cloud. You can only deploy virtual servers in the public cloud. You can extend a private cloud by\ndeploying virtual servers in a public cloud. This would create a hybrid cloud.\nBox 2: Yes -\nA hybrid cloud is a combination of a private cloud and public cloud. Therefore, to create a hybrid cloud, you must deploy resources to a public\ncloud.\nBox 3: No.\nIt is not true that a private cloud must be disconnected from the Internet. Private clouds can be and most commonly are connected to the\nInternet. ג€Private cloudג€ means that the physical servers are managed by you. It does not mean that it is disconnected from the Internet.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "You cannot add physical servers to the public cloud",
        "A hybrid cloud is a combination of a private cloud and public cloud"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 63,
      "original_number": "63",
      "question": "You have 50 virtual machines hosted on-premises and 50 virtual machines hosted in Azure. The on-premises virtual machines and the Azure\nvirtual machines connect to each other.\nWhich type of cloud model is this?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "hybrid"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "private"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "public"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nR",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/overview/what-is-hybrid-cloud-computing/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 64,
      "original_number": "64",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nA PaaS solution does not provide access to the operating system. The Azure Web Apps service provides an environment for you to host your\nweb applications.\nBehind the scenes, the web apps are hosted on virtual machines running IIS. However, you have no direct access to the virtual machine, the\noperating system or\nIIS.\nBox 2: Yes -\nBox 3: Yes -\nA PaaS solution that hosts web apps in Azure does provide the ability to scale the platform automatically. This is known as autoscaling. Behind\nthe scenes, the web apps are hosted on virtual machines running IIS. Autoscaling means adding more load balanced virtual machines to host\nthe web apps.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "A PaaS solution does not provide access to the operating system",
        "Box 3: Yes -\nA PaaS solution that hosts web apps in Azure does provide the ability to scale the platform automatically"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 65,
      "original_number": "65",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYour company plans to migrate all its data and resources to Azure.\nThe company's migration plan states that only Platform as a Service (PaaS) solutions must be used in Azure.\nYou need to deploy an Azure environment that meets the company migration plan.\nSolution: You create Azure virtual machines, Azure SQL databases, and Azure Storage accounts.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nP",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/overview/what-is-paas/\nhttps://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/overview/what-is-iaas/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 66,
      "original_number": "66",
      "question": "Your company plans to deploy several custom applications to Azure. The applications will provide invoicing services to the customers of the\ncompany. Each application will have several prerequisite applications and services installed.\nYou need to recommend a cloud deployment solution for all the applications.\nWhat should you recommend?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Software as a Service (SaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Platform as a Service (PaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Infrastructure as a Service (laaS)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nI",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/overview/what-is-iaas/\nhttps://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/overview/what-is-saas/\nhttps://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/overview/what-is-paas/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 67,
      "original_number": "67",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "Yes",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nBuilding a data center infrastructure is capital expenditure, not operation expenditure.\nBox 2: Yes -\nOpEx is ongoing costs (costs of operations) such as staff salaries.\nBox 2: Yes -\nOpEx is ongoing costs (costs of operations) such as leasing software. If you purchased software as a one-off purchase, that would be CapEx,\nbut leasing software is ongoing so it's OpEx.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Building a data center infrastructure is capital expenditure, not operation expenditure.",
        "OpEx is ongoing costs (costs of operations) such as staff salaries.",
        "OpEx is ongoing costs (costs of operations) such as leasing software"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 68,
      "original_number": "68",
      "question": "Azure Cosmos DB is an example of a platform as a service (PaaS) cloud database provider.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Cosmos DB is an example of"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "platform as a service (PaaS)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Azure Cosmos DB is an example of a platform as a service (PaaS) cloud database provider.",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 69,
      "original_number": "69",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/overview/what-is-saas/\nhttps://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/overview/what-is-iaas/\nhttps://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/overview/what-is-paas/",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 70,
      "original_number": "70",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nBox 2: No -\nEach resource can exist in only one resource group.\nBox 3: Yes -\nResources from multiple different regions can be placed in a resource group. The resource group only contains metadata about the resources it\ncontains.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Box 2: No -\nEach resource can exist in only one resource group.",
        "Resources from multiple different regions can be placed in a resource group"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 71,
      "original_number": "71",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-sql/azure-sql-iaas-vs-paas-what-is-overview https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cosmos-\ndb/account-databases-containers-items https://www.red-gate.com/simple-talk/cloud/azure/overview-of-azure-cosmos-db",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 72,
      "original_number": "72",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 73,
      "original_number": "73",
      "question": "Your company plans to migrate all its data and resources to Azure.\nThe company's migration plan states that only Platform as a Service (PaaS) solutions must be used in Azure.\nYou need to deploy an Azure environment that meets the company's migration plan.\nWhat should you create?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure virtual machines, Azure SQL databases, and Azure Storage accounts."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an Azure App Service and Azure virtual machines that have Microsoft SQL Server installed."
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "an Azure App Service and Azure SQL databases."
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure storage accounts and web server in Azure virtual machines."
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nA",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 74,
      "original_number": "74",
      "question": "What does a customer provide in a software as a service (SaaS) model?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "application data"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "data storage"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "compute resources"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "application software"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nS",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-in/overview/what-is-saas/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 75,
      "original_number": "75",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/overview/what-is-iaas/\nhttps://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/overview/what-is-paas/\nhttps://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/overview/what-is-saas/",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 76,
      "original_number": "76",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 77,
      "original_number": "77",
      "question": "What is the +rst stage in the Microsoft Cloud Adoption Framework for Azure?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Adopt the cloud."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Make a plan."
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Ready your organization."
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "De+ne your strategy."
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nR",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cloud-adoption-framework/overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 78,
      "original_number": "78",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "No"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nYou cannot add physical servers to the public cloud. You can only deploy virtual servers in the public cloud. You can extend a private cloud by\ndeploying virtual servers in a public cloud. This would create a hybrid cloud.\nBox 2: No -\nA private cloud exists in cyberspace and is accessed via the internet.\nBox 3: Yes.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "You cannot add physical servers to the public cloud",
        "A private cloud exists in cyberspace and is accessed via the internet."
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 79,
      "original_number": "79",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "Yes",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nVirtual Machines works.\nBox 2: Yes -\nSimply put, cloud computing is the delivery of computing servicesג€\"including servers, storage, databases, networking, software, analytics, and\nintelligenceג€\"over the Internet (ג€the cloudג€) to offer faster innovation, jexible resources, and economies of scale.\nBox 3: Yes -",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Virtual Machines works.",
        "Simply put, cloud computing is the delivery of computing servicesג€\"including servers, storage, databases, networking, software, analytics, and\nintelligenceג€\"over the Internet (ג€the cloudג€) to offe",
        "Reference:\nhttps://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/overview/what-is-cloud-computing/"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 80,
      "original_number": "80",
      "question": "Match the cloud computing bene+ts to the correct descriptions.\nTo answer, drag the appropriate bene+t from the column on the left to its description on the right. Each bene+t may be used once, more than once,\nor not at all.\nNOTE: Each correct match is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 81,
      "original_number": "81",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "Y",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/site-recovery/azure-to-azure-tutorial-enable-replication",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 82,
      "original_number": "82",
      "question": "You plan to use Azure to host two apps named App1 and App2. The apps must meet the following requirements:\n\n→ You must be able to modify the code of App1.\n→ Administrative effort to manage the operating system of App1 must be minimized.\n→ App2 must run interactively with the operating system of the server.\n\nWhich type of cloud service should you use for each app? To answer, select the appropriate options in the answer area.\n\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Box 1: Azure Platform as a service (PaaS)\nOrganizations typically use PaaS for these scenarios:\nDevelopment framework. PaaS provides a framework that developers can build upon to develop or customize cloud-based applications. Similar\nto the way you create an Excel macro, PaaS lets developers create applications using built-in software components. Cloud features such as\nscalability, high-availability, and multi-tenant capability are included, reducing the amount of coding that developers must do.\nBox 2:\nSoftware as a service (SaaS) allows users to connect to and use cloud-based apps over the Internet. Common examples are email, calendaring,\nand ohce tools\n\n(such as Microsoft Ohce 365).\nSaaS provides a complete software solution that you purchase on a pay-as-you-go basis from a cloud service provider. You rent the use of an\napp for your organization, and your users connect to it over the Internet, usually with a web browser. All of the underlying infrastructure,\nmiddleware, app software,",
      "questionType": "MATCHING",
      "matchingItems": [
        {
          "item": "App1",
          "options": [
            "Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS)",
            "Platform as a Service (PaaS)",
            "Software as a Service (SaaS)"
          ],
          "answer": "Platform as a Service (PaaS)"
        },
        {
          "item": "App2",
          "options": [
            "Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS)",
            "Platform as a Service (PaaS)",
            "Software as a Service (SaaS)"
          ],
          "answer": "Infrastructure as a Service (IaaS)"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 83,
      "original_number": "83",
      "question": "You have an accounting application named App1 that uses a legacy database.\nYou plan to move App1 to the cloud.\nWhich service model should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "platform as a service (PaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "infrastructure as a service (IaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "software as a service (SaaS)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nC",
      "explanation": "https://techtaalk.com/microsoft-azure-for-legacy-application-modernization/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 84,
      "original_number": "84",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://www.salesforce.com/in/saas/",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 85,
      "original_number": "85",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/architecture/hybrid/deployments/solution-deployment-guide-cross-cloud-scaling-onprem-data",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 86,
      "original_number": "86",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/overview/what-is-paas/",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 87,
      "original_number": "87",
      "question": "Which cloud computing model includes on-premises and cloud-based resources?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "hybrid"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "public"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "private"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nA",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/overview/what-is-hybrid-cloud-computing/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 88,
      "original_number": "88",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machine-scale-sets/virtual-machine-scale-sets-autoscale-overview\nhttps://www.netreo.com/cloud-automation/what-is-azure-elasticity-as-a-service/",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 89,
      "original_number": "89",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 90,
      "original_number": "90",
      "question": "Which term represents the ability to increase the computing capacity of a virtual machine by adding memory or CPUs?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "agility"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "vertical scaling"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "horizontal scaling"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "elasticity"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nV",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machine-scale-sets/virtual-machine-scale-sets-vertical-scale-reprovision",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 91,
      "original_number": "91",
      "question": "What are two bene+ts of cloud computing? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "enables the rapid provisioning of resources"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "has increased administrative complexity"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "has the same con+guration options as on-premises"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "shifts capital expenditures (CAPEX) to operating expenditures (OPEX)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "AD\nA",
      "explanation": "https://www.protechtraining.com/blog/post/top-5-bene+ts-of-microsoft-azure-for-business-934 https://www.azureguru.org/capex-vs-opex/#",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 92,
      "original_number": "92",
      "question": "What is a feature of an Azure virtual network?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "resource cost analysis"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "packet inspection"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "geo-redundancy"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "isolation and segmentation"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nI",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/architecture/framework/security/design-network-segmentation",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 93,
      "original_number": "93",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/learn/modules/fundamental-azure-concepts/bene+ts-of-cloud-computing",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 94,
      "original_number": "94",
      "question": "Match the cloud computing bene+ts to the appropriate descriptions.\nTo answer, drag the appropriate bene+t from the column on the left to its description on the right. Each bene+t may be used once, more than once,\n\nor not at all.\nNOTE: Each correct match is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/learn/modules/fundamental-azure-concepts/bene+ts-of-cloud-computing",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 95,
      "original_number": "95",
      "question": "Which cloud computing bene+t provides continuous user access to a cloud-based application with minimal downtime?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "agility"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "scalability"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "elasticity"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "high availability"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 96,
      "original_number": "96",
      "question": "You need to identify the type of failure for which an Azure Availability Zone can be used to protect access to Azure services.\nWhat should you identify?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a physical server failure"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an Azure region failure"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a storage failure"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "an Azure data center failure"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machines/availability",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 97,
      "original_number": "97",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nYou plan to extend your company's network to Azure.\nThe network contains a VPN appliance that uses an IP address of 131.107.200.1.\n\nYou need to create an Azure resource that de+nes the VPN appliance in Azure.\nWhich Azure resource should you create? To answer, select the appropriate resource in the answer area.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "A L",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/vpn-gateway/vpn-gateway-howto-site-to-site-resource-manager-portal",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 98,
      "original_number": "98",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYou plan to deploy several Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to ensure that the services running on the virtual machines are available if a single data center fails.\nSolution: You deploy the virtual machines to two or more resource groups.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-resource-manager/management/overview#resource-groups",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 99,
      "original_number": "99",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYou plan to deploy several Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to ensure that the services running on the virtual machines are available if a single data center fails.\nSolution: You deploy the virtual machines to a scale set.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nT",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machine-scale-sets/availability",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 100,
      "original_number": "100",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nAn Azure AD tenant can have multiple subscriptions but an Azure subscription can only be associated with one Azure AD tenant.\nBox 2: Yes -\nBox 3: No -\nIf your subscription expires, you lose access to all the other resources associated with the subscription. However, the Azure AD directory\nremains in Azure. You can associate and manage the directory using a different Azure subscription.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "An Azure AD tenant can have multiple subscriptions but an Azure subscription can only be associated with one Azure AD tenant.",
        "Box 3: No -\nIf your subscription expires, you lose access to all the other resources associated with the subscription"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 101,
      "original_number": "101",
      "question": "This question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.\nResource groups provide organizations with the ability to manage the compliance of Azure resources across multiple subscriptions.\nInstructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed`. If the statement is incorrect, select the\nanswer choice that makes the statement correct.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "No change is needed"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Management groups"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure policies"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure App Service plans"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/governance/policy/overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 102,
      "original_number": "102",
      "question": "Your company plans to migrate to Azure.\nThe company has several departments. All the Azure resources used by each department will be managed by a department administrator.\nWhat are two possible techniques to segment Azure for the departments? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "multiple subscriptions"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "multiple Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) directories"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "multiple regions"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "multiple resource groups"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "AD\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cost-management-billing/manage/create-subscription https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cost-\nmanagement-billing/manage/add-change-subscription-administrator",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 103,
      "original_number": "103",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "Yes",
        "No",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: Yes -\nYou can use the same account to manage multiple subscriptions. You can create an additional subscription for your account in the Azure\nportal. You may want an additional subscription to avoid hitting subscription limits, to create separate environments for security, or to isolate\ndata for compliance reasons.\nBox 2: No -\nYou cannot merge two subscriptions into a single subscription. However, you can move some Azure resources from one subscription to\nanother. You can also transfer ownership of a subscription and change the billing type for a subscription.\nBox 3: Yes -\nA company can have multiple subscriptions and store resources in the different subscriptions. However, a resource instance can exist in only\n\none subscription.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "You can use the same account to manage multiple subscriptions",
        "You cannot merge two subscriptions into a single subscription",
        "A company can have multiple subscriptions and store resources in the different subscriptions"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 104,
      "original_number": "104",
      "question": "You have several virtual machines in an Azure subscription. You create a new subscription.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "The virtual machines cannot be moved to the new subscription"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "The virtual machines can be moved to the new subscription"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "The virtual machines can be moved to the new subscription only if they are all in the same resource group"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "The virtual machines can be moved to the new subscription only if they run Windows Server 2016"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "You can move a VM and its associated resources to a different subscription by using the Azure portal.\nMoving between subscriptions can be handy if you originally created a VM in a personal subscription and now want to move it to your\ncompany's subscription to continue your work. You do not need to start the VM in order to move it and it should continue to run during the\nmove.",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 105,
      "original_number": "105",
      "question": "You have an Azure environment that contains multiple Azure virtual machines.\nYou plan to implement a solution that enables the client computers on your on-premises network to communicate to the Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to recommend which Azure resources must be created for the planned solution.\nWhich two Azure resources should you include in the recommendation? Each correct answer presents part of the solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a virtual network gateway"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "a load balancer"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "an application gateway"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a virtual network"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "a gateway subnet"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "AE\nT",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/ohce365/enterprise/connect-an-on-premises-network-to-a-microsoft-azure-virtual-network",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 106,
      "original_number": "106",
      "question": "You attempt to create several managed Microsoft SQL Server instances in an Azure environment and receive a message that you must increase\nyour Azure subscription limits.\nWhat should you do to increase the limits?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Create a service health alert"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Upgrade your support plan"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Modify an Azure policy"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Create a new support request"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nM",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/sql-database/sql-database-managed-instance-resource-limits#obtaining-a-larger-quota-for-sql-\nmanaged-instance",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 107,
      "original_number": "107",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "No",
        "No"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nYou can assign service administrators and co-administrators in the Azure Portal but there can only be one account administrator.\nBox 2: No -\nYou need an Azure Active Directory account to manage a subscription, not a Microsoft account.\nAn account is created in the Azure Active Directory when you create the subscription. Further accounts can be created in the Azure Active\nDirectory to manage the subscription.\nBox 3: No -\nResource groups are logical containers for Azure resources. However, resource groups do not contain subscriptions. Subscriptions contain\nresource groups.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "You can assign service administrators and co-administrators in the Azure Portal but there can only be one account administrator.",
        "You need an Azure Active Directory account to manage a subscription, not a Microsoft account",
        "Resource groups are logical containers for Azure resources"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 108,
      "original_number": "108",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "No",
        "No"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nNot all Azure regions support availability zones.\nBox 2: No -\nAvailability zones can be used with many Azure services, not just VMs.\nBox 3: No -\nAvailability Zones are unique physical locations within a single Azure region.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Not all Azure regions support availability zones.",
        "Availability zones can be used with many Azure services, not just VMs.",
        "Availability Zones are unique physical locations within a single Azure region."
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 109,
      "original_number": "109",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nYou plan to create an Azure virtual machine.\nYou need to identify which storage service must be used to store the unmanaged data disks of the virtual machine.\nWhat should you identify? To answer, select the appropriate service in the answer area.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/storage/blobs/storage-blob-pageblob-overview",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 110,
      "original_number": "110",
      "question": "Your company plans to move several servers to Azure.\nThe company's compliance policy states that a server named FinServer must be on a separate network segment.\nYou are evaluating which Azure services can be used to meet the compliance policy requirements.\nWhich Azure solution should you recommend?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a resource group for FinServer and another resource group for all the other servers"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "a virtual network for FinServer and another virtual network for all the other servers"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a VPN for FinServer and a virtual network gateway for each other server"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "one resource group for all the servers and a resource lock for FinServer"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nN",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-network/virtual-network-vnet-plan-design-arm",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 111,
      "original_number": "111",
      "question": "You plan to map a network drive from several computers that run Windows 10 to Azure Storage.\nYou need to create a storage solution in Azure for the planned mapped drive.\nWhat should you create?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "an Azure SQL database"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "a virtual machine data disk"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a File service in a storage account"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a Blob service in a storage account"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/storage/+les/storage-how-to-use-+les-windows",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 112,
      "original_number": "112",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nYou plan to implement an Azure database solution.\nYou need to implement a database solution that meets the following requirements:\n✑ Can add data concurrently from multiple regions\n✑ Can store JSON documents\n\nWhich database service should you deploy? To answer, select the appropriate service in the answer area.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cosmos-db/introduction https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-functions/functions-integrate-\nstore-unstructured-data-cosmosdb?tabs=csharp",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 113,
      "original_number": "113",
      "question": "Your company plans to start using Azure and will migrate all its network resources to Azure.\nYou need to start the planning process by exploring Azure.\nWhat should you create +rst?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a subscription"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "a resource group"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a virtual network"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a management group"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nT",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/ohce365/enterprise/subscriptions-licenses-accounts-and-tenants-for-microsoft-cloud-offerings",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 114,
      "original_number": "114",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "No",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nAzure resources deployed to a single resource group can be located in different regions. The resource group only contains metadata about the\nresources it contains.\nWhen creating a resource group, you need to provide a location for that resource group. You may be wondering, \"Why does a resource group\nneed a location?\nAnd, if the resources can have different locations than the resource group, why does the resource group location matter at all?\" The resource\ngroup stores metadata about the resources. When you specify a location for the resource group, you're specifying where that metadata is\nstored. For compliance reasons, you may need to ensure that your data is stored in a particular region.\nBox 2: No -\nTags for Resources are not inherited by default from their Resource Group\n\nBox 3: Yes -\nA resource group can be used to scope access control for administrative actions. By default, permissions set at the resource level are inherited\nby the resources in the resource group.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Azure resources deployed to a single resource group can be located in different regions",
        "Tags for Resources are not inherited by default from their Resource Group",
        "A resource group can be used to scope access control for administrative actions"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 115,
      "original_number": "115",
      "question": "Data that is stored in the Archive access tier of an Azure Storage account _______",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "can be accessed at any time by using azcopy.exe"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "can only be read by using Azure Backup"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "must be restored before the data can be accessed"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "must be rehydrated before the data can be accessed"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "Azure storage offers different access tiers: hot, cool and archive.\nThe archive access tier has the lowest storage cost. But it has higher data retrieval costs compared to the hot and cool tiers. Data in the archive\ntier can take several hours to retrieve.\nWhile a blob is in archive storage, the blob data is oline and can't be read, overwritten, or modi+ed. To read or download a blob in archive, you\nmust +rst rehydrate it to an online tier.\nExample usage scenarios for the archive access tier include:\n✑ Long-term backup, secondary backup, and archival datasets\n✑ Original (raw) data that must be preserved, even after it has been processed into +nal usable form.\n✑ Compliance and archival data that needs to be stored for a long time and is hardly ever accessed.",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 116,
      "original_number": "116",
      "question": "You plan to deploy a critical line-of-business application to Azure.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure offers industry best"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure region"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure virtual machine"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "You need a minimum of two virtual machines with each one located in a different availability zone.\nAvailability Zones is a high-availability offering that protects your applications and data from datacenter failures. Availability Zones are unique\nphysical locations within an Azure region. Each zone is made up of one or more datacenters equipped with independent power, cooling, and\nnetworking. To ensure resiliency, there's a minimum of three separate zones in all enabled regions. The physical sep",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 117,
      "original_number": "117",
      "question": "Which Azure service should you use to collect events from multiple resources into a centralized repository?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Event Hubs"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Analysis Services"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Monitor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Stream Analytics"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/event-hubs/event-hubs-about",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 118,
      "original_number": "118",
      "question": "An Availability Zone in Azure has physically separate locations _______",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "across two continents"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "within a single Azure region"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "within multiple Azure regions"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "within a single Azure datacenter"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Availability Zones is a high-availability offering that protects your applications and data from datacenter failures. Availability Zones are unique\nphysical locations within an Azure region.",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 119,
      "original_number": "119",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "Yes",
        "No",
        "No"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: Yes -\nThere are different replication options available with a storage account. The 'minimum' replication option is Locally Redundant Storage (LRS).\nWith LRS, data is replicated synchronously three times within the primary region.\nBox 2: No -\nData is not backed up automatically to another Azure Data Center although it can be depending on the replication option con+gured for the\naccount. Locally\nRedundant Storage (LRS) is the default which maintains three copies of the data in the data center.\nGeo-redundant storage (GRS) has cross-regional replication to protect against regional outages. Data is replicated synchronously three times in\nthe primary region, then replicated asynchronously to the secondary region.\nBox 3: No -\nThe limits are much higher than that. The current storage limit is 2 PB for US and Europe, and 500 TB for all other regions (including the UK)\nwith no limit on the number of +les.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "There are different replication options available with a storage account",
        "Data is not backed up automatically to another Azure Data Center although it can be depending on the replication option con+gured for the\naccount",
        "The limits are much higher than that"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 120,
      "original_number": "120",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "No",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nNot all Azure regions support availability zones.\nBox 2: No -\nRegions that support availability zones support Linux virtual machines.\nBox 3: Yes -\nAvailability Zones is a high-availability offering that protects your applications and data from datacenter failures. Availability Zones are unique\nphysical locations within an Azure region. Each zone is made up of one or more datacenters equipped with independent power, cooling, and\nnetworking. To ensure resiliency, there's a minimum of three separate zones in all enabled regions. The physical separation of Availability Zones\nwithin a region protects applications and data from datacenter failures. Zone-redundant services replicate your applications and data across\nAvailability Zones to protect from single-points-of-failure. With Availability\nZones, Azure offers industry best 99.99% VM uptime SLA.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Not all Azure regions support availability zones.",
        "Regions that support availability zones support Linux virtual machines.",
        "Availability Zones is a high-availability offering that protects your applications and data from datacenter failures"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 121,
      "original_number": "121",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "Yes",
        "No"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nNorth America has several Azure regions, including West US, Central US, South Central US, East Us, and Canada East.\nBox 2: Yes -\nA region is a set of datacenters deployed within a latency-de+ned perimeter and connected through a dedicated regional low-latency network.\nBox 3: No -\nOutbound data transfer is charged at the normal rate and inbound data transfer is free.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "North America has several Azure regions, including West US, Central US, South Central US, East Us, and Canada East.",
        "A region is a set of datacenters deployed within a latency-de+ned perimeter and connected through a dedicated regional low-latency network.",
        "Outbound data transfer is charged at the normal rate and inbound data transfer is free."
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 122,
      "original_number": "122",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYou plan to deploy several Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to ensure that the services running on the virtual machines are available if a single data center fails.\nSolution: You deploy the virtual machines to two or more scale sets.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nT",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machine-scale-sets/availability",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 123,
      "original_number": "123",
      "question": "You need to be noti+ed when Microsoft plans to perform maintenance that can affect the resources deployed to an Azure subscription.\nWhat should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Monitor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Service Health"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Advisor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Microsoft Trust Center"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/service-health/overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 124,
      "original_number": "124",
      "question": "Match the Azure Services service to the correct description.\nInstructions: To answer, drag the appropriate service from the column on the left to its description on the right. Each service may be used once,\nmore than once, or not at all.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure-sphere/product-overview/what-is-azure-sphere https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/iot-\ncentral/core/overview-iot-central https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/iot-hub/about-iot-hub",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 125,
      "original_number": "125",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-desktop/overview",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 126,
      "original_number": "126",
      "question": "https://blog.abouttmc.com/azure-cloud-total-cost-of-ownership _______",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Option A (확인 필요)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Option B (확인 필요)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Option C (확인 필요)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Option D (확인 필요)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Reference:\nhttps://blog.abouttmc.com/azure-cloud-total-cost-of-ownership",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 127,
      "original_number": "127",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machines/windows/manage-availability",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 128,
      "original_number": "128",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "No"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nA subscription can have multiple administrators, but there can only be one account administrator.\nBox 3: No -\nA subscription can contain multiple resource groups but a resource group can only belong to one subscription. Resource groups can contain\nmultiple resources.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "A subscription can have multiple administrators, but there can only be one account administrator.",
        "A subscription can contain multiple resource groups but a resource group can only belong to one subscription"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 129,
      "original_number": "129",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 130,
      "original_number": "130",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/active-directory/enterprise-users/groups-dynamic-membership https://petri.com/understanding-\nhybrid-azure-active-directory-join",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 131,
      "original_number": "131",
      "question": "You plan to deploy several Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to ensure that the services running on the virtual machines remain available if a single data center fails.\nWhat are two possible solutions? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Deploy the virtual machines to two or more availability zones."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Deploy the virtual machines to two or more resource groups."
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Deploy the virtual machines to a scale set."
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Deploy the virtual machines to two or more regions."
        }
      ],
      "answer": "AD\nR",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machine-scale-sets/overview https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-\nmachines/windows/regions",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 132,
      "original_number": "132",
      "question": "You plan to deploy 20 virtual machines to an Azure environment. To ensure that a virtual machine named VM1 cannot connect to the other virtual machines, VM1 must _______",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "be deployed to a separate virtual network"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "run a different operating system than the other virtual machines"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "be deployed to a separate resource group"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "have two network interfaces"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Azure automatically routes trahc between subnets in a virtual network. Therefore, all virtual machines in a virtual network can connect to the\nother virtual machines in the same virtual network. Even if the virtual machines are on separate subnets within the virtual network, they can still\ncommunicate with each other.\nTo ensure that a virtual machine cannot connect to the other virtual machines, the virtual machine must be deployed to a separate virtual\nnetwork.",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 133,
      "original_number": "133",
      "question": "Match the Azure service to the appropriate description.\nTo answer, drag the appropriate service from the column on the left to its description on the right. Each service may be used once, more than\nonce, or not at all.\nNOTE: Each correct match is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 134,
      "original_number": "134",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/storage/blobs/storage-blob-storage-tiers",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 135,
      "original_number": "135",
      "question": "What is the most severe failure from which an Azure Availability Zone can be used to protect access to Azure service?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a physical server failure"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an Azure region failure"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a storage failure"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "an Azure data center failure"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machines/availability",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 136,
      "original_number": "136",
      "question": "You need to purchase a third-party virtual security appliance that you will deploy to an Azure subscription.\nWhat should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure subscriptions"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Security Center"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Marketplace"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Microsoft Store"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nR",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cost-management-billing/manage/ea-azure-marketplace",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 137,
      "original_number": "137",
      "question": "Match the serverless solution to the correct characteristic.\nTo answer drag the appropriate serverless solution from the column on the left to its characteristic on the right Each serverless solution may be\n\nTo answer, drag the appropriate serverless solution from the column on the left to its characteristic on the right. Each serverless solution may be\nused once, more than once, or not at all.\nNOTE: Each correct match is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/logic-apps/logic-apps-overview https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-functions/functions-\noverview",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 138,
      "original_number": "138",
      "question": "Match the Azure governance feature to the correct description.\nInstructions: To answer, drag the appropriate feature from the column on the left to its description on the right. Each feature may be used once,\nmore than once, or not at all.\nNOTE: Each correct match is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/governance/blueprints/overview https://docs.microsoft.com/en-\nus/azure/governance/policy/overview https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-resource-manager/management/tag-resources?\ntabs=json https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-resource-manager/management/lock-resources?tabs=json",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 139,
      "original_number": "139",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/availability-zones/az-overview",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 140,
      "original_number": "140",
      "question": "Match the Azure services to the correct descriptions.\nInstructions: To answer, drag the appropriate Azure service from the column on the left to its description on the right. Each service may be used\nonce, more than once, or not at all.\nNOTE: Each correct match is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/container-instances\nhttps://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/app-service/\nhttps://revdebug.com/blog/what-are-azure-functions",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 141,
      "original_number": "141",
      "question": "To answer, select the appropriate option in the answer area.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure portal"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure portal to manage the resource group containing the VM to move"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Box: The virtual machines can be moved to the new subscription.\nYou can move a VM and its associated resources to a different subscription by using the Azure portal.\nNote: Repeat the process below for each Resource Group containing the VMs.\n1. Go to the Azure portal to manage the resource group containing the VM to move. Search for and select Resource groups.\n2. Choose the resource group containing the VM that you would like to move.\n3. At the top of the page for the resource group, select Move ",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 142,
      "original_number": "142",
      "question": "You need to purchase a third-party virtual security appliance that you will deploy to an Azure subscription.\nWhat should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure subscriptions"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Microsoft Defender for Cloud"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Marketplace"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Microsoft Store"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nY",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/security/fundamentals/network-overview https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cost-management-\nbilling/manage/ea-azure-marketplace",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 143,
      "original_number": "143",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "M",
      "explanation": "https://www.zdnet.com/article/microsofts-azure-sphere-its-linux-based-microcontroller-plus-cloud-service-hits-general-availability/",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 144,
      "original_number": "144",
      "question": "You plan to deploy a service to Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to ensure that the service will be available if a datacenter fails.\nWhat should you use as part of the virtual machine deployment?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "availability sets"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "proximity placement groups"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "host groups"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "availability zones"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/availability-zones/az-overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 145,
      "original_number": "145",
      "question": "Your company has an Azure subscription that contains resources in several regions.\nYou need to ensure that administrators can only create resources in those regions.\nWhat should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a read-only lock"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an Azure policy"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a management group"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a reservation"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 146,
      "original_number": "146",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/availability-zones/az-overview",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 147,
      "original_number": "147",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/download/details.aspx?id=57159",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 148,
      "original_number": "148",
      "question": "What is the function of a Site-to-Site VPN?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "provides a secure connection between a computer on a public network and the corporate network"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "provides a dedicated private connection to Azure that does NOT travel over the internet"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "provides a connection from an on-premises VPN device to an Azure VPN gateway"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nA S",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/vpn-gateway/vpn-gateway-howto-site-to-site-classic-portal",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 149,
      "original_number": "149",
      "question": "Match the cloud service models to the appropriate offerings.\nTo answer, drag the appropriate model from the column on the left to its offering on the right. Each model may be used once, more than once, or\nnot at all.\nNOTE: Each correct match is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/overview/what-is-paas/\nhttps://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/blog/infrastructure-as-a-service-series-virtual-machines-and-windows/ https://pipol.com/what-is-microsoft-\ndynamics-365",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 150,
      "original_number": "150",
      "question": "Match the cloud service models to the appropriate solutions.\nTo answer, drag the appropriate cloud service model from the column on the left to its solution on the right Each cloud service model may be used\nonce, more than once, or not at all.\nNOTE: Each correct match is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/overview/what-is-iaas\nhttps://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/overview/what-is-paas/",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 151,
      "original_number": "151",
      "question": "You need to manage containers.\nWhich two services can you use? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Virtual Desktop"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure virtual machines"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Functions"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Container Instances"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "DE\nR",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/container-instances/\nhttps://cloudacademy.com/blog/azure-kubernetes-service-aks-what-is-it-and-why-do-we-use-it",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 152,
      "original_number": "152",
      "question": "A resource group is a logical container for Azure resources. Resource groups make the management of Azure resources easier.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure resources"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure resources easier"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "A resource group is a logical container for Azure resources. Resource groups make the management of Azure resources easier.\nWith a resource group, you can allow a user to manage all resources in the resource group, such as virtual machines, websites, and subnets.\nThe permissions you apply to the resource group apply to all resources contained in the resource group.",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 153,
      "original_number": "153",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYou plan to deploy several Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to ensure that the services running on the virtual machines are available if a single data center fails.\nSolution: You deploy the virtual machines to two or more availability zones.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machine-scale-sets/availability",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 154,
      "original_number": "154",
      "question": "This question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.\nOne of the bene+ts of Azure SQL Data Warehouse is that high availability is built into the platform.\nInstructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed`. If the statement is incorrect, select the\nanswer choice that makes the statement correct.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "No change is needed"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "automatic scaling"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "data compression"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "versioning"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/sql-data-warehouse/sql-data-warehouse-overview-faq",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 155,
      "original_number": "155",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYou plan to deploy several Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to ensure that the services running on the virtual machines are available if a single data center fails.\nSolution: You deploy the virtual machines to two or more regions.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nB",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machines/windows/regions",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 156,
      "original_number": "156",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/architecture/guide/technology-choices/compute-decision-tree",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 157,
      "original_number": "157",
      "question": "At which OSI layer does ExpressRoute operate?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Layer 2"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Layer 3"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Layer 5"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Layer 7"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nE",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/architecture/reference-architectures/hybrid-networking/expressroute",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 158,
      "original_number": "158",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-monitor/app/app-insights-overview",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 159,
      "original_number": "159",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "Yes",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nA resource can interact with resources in other resource groups.\nBox 2: Yes -\nDeleting the resource group will remove the resource group as well as all the resources in that resource group. This can be useful for the\nmanagement of resources. For example, a virtual machine has several components (the VM itself, virtual disks, network adapter etc.). By\nplacing the VM in its own resource group, you can delete the VM along with all its associated components by deleting the resource group.\nAnother example is when creating a test environment. You could place the entire test environment (Network components, virtual machines etc.)\nin one resource group. You can then delete the entire test environment by deleting the resource group.\nBox 3: Yes -\nResources from multiple different regions can be placed in a resource group. The resource group only contains metadata about the resources it\ncontains.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "A resource can interact with resources in other resource groups.",
        "Deleting the resource group will remove the resource group as well as all the resources in that resource group",
        "Resources from multiple different regions can be placed in a resource group"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 160,
      "original_number": "160",
      "question": "You plan to store 20 TB of data in Azure. The data will be accessed infrequently and visualized by using Microsoft Power BI.\nYou need to recommend a storage solution for the data.\nWhich two solutions should you recommend? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Data Lake"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Cosmos DB"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure SQL Data Warehouse"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure SQL Database"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "Azure Database for PostgreSQL"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "AC\nY",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/data-lake-store/data-lake-store-power-bi https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/solutions/data-lake/\nhttps://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/data-lake-store/data-lake-store-power-bi",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 161,
      "original_number": "161",
      "question": "You have an Azure environment that contains 10 web apps. To which URL should you connect to manage all the Azure resources? To answer,",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure environment that contains"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure portal is"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure portal is https"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure resources"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "The Azure portal is a web-based management interface where you can view and manage all your Azure resources in one uni+ed hub, including\nweb apps, databases, virtual machines, virtual networks, storage and Visual Studio team projects.\nThe URL of the Azure portal is https://portal.azure.com.",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 162,
      "original_number": "162",
      "question": "Arrange the storage account redundancy options from the least redundant to the most redundant. To answer, move all options from the list of\noptions to the answer area and arrange them in the correct order.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 163,
      "original_number": "163",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 164,
      "original_number": "164",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nAn Azure administrator plans to run a PowerShell script that creates Azure resources.\nYou need to recommend which computer con+guration to use to run the script.\nSolution: Run the script from a computer that runs Linux and has the Azure CLI tools installed.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nA P",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/powershell/scripting/components/ise/how-to-write-and-run-scripts-in-the-windows-powershell-ise?\nview=powershell-6",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 165,
      "original_number": "165",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nAn Azure administrator plans to run a PowerShell script that creates Azure resources.\nYou need to recommend which computer con+guration to use to run the script.\nSolution: Run the script from a computer that runs Chrome OS and uses Azure Cloud Shell.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nA P",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cloud-shell/quickstart-powershell",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 166,
      "original_number": "166",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "Yes",
        "Yes",
        "No"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: Yes -\nAzure Service Health consists of three components: Azure Status, Azure Service Heath and Azure Resource Health.\nAzure service health provides a personalized view of the health of the Azure services and regions you're using. This is the best place to look for\nservice impacting communications about outages, planned maintenance activities, and other health advisories because the authenticated\nAzure Service Health experience knows which services and resources you currently use.\nTo view the health of all other services available in Azure, you would use the Azure Status component of Azure Service Health. Azure status\ninforms you of service outages in Azure on the Azure Status page. The page is a global view of the health of all Azure services across all Azure\nregions.\nBox 2: Yes -\nThe best way to use Service Health is to set up Service Health alerts to notify you via your preferred communication channels when service\nissues, planned maintenance, or other changes may affect the A",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Azure Service Health consists of three components: Azure Status, Azure Service Heath and Azure Resource Health",
        "The best way to use Service Health is to set up Service Health alerts to notify you via your preferred communication channels when service\nissues, planned maintenance, or other changes may affect the ",
        "You can use Resource Health to view the health of a virtual machine"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 167,
      "original_number": "167",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nAn Azure administrator plans to run a PowerShell script that creates Azure resources.\nYou need to recommend which computer con+guration to use to run the script.\nSolution: Run the script from a computer that runs macOS and has PowerShell Core 6.0 installed.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nA P",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/powershell/scripting/components/ise/how-to-write-and-run-scripts-in-the-windows-powershell-ise?\nview=powershell-6",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 168,
      "original_number": "168",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nYou need to view a list of planned maintenance events that can affect the availability of an Azure subscription.\nWhich blade should you use from the Azure portal? To answer, select the appropriate blade in the answer area.\n\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "O",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 169,
      "original_number": "169",
      "question": "Match the Azure service to the correct de+nition.\nInstructions: To answer, drag the appropriate Azure service from the column on the left to its description on the right. Each service may be used\nonce, more than once, or not at all.\nNOTE: Each correct match is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-monitor/app/app-insights-overview https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/overview/what-is-\ndevops/ https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/advisor/advisor-overview https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cognitive-\nservices/welcome",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 170,
      "original_number": "170",
      "question": "Match the Azure service to the correct description.\nInstructions: To answer, drag the appropriate Azure service from the column on the left to its description on the right. Each service may be used\nonce, more than once, or not at all.\nNOTE: Each correct match is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/sql-database/\nhttps://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/sql-data-warehouse/sql-data-warehouse-overview-what-is https://docs.microsoft.com/bs-latn-\nba/azure/hdinsight/hadoop/apache-hadoop-introduction https://www.blue-granite.com/blog/is-azure-sql-data-warehouse-a-good-+t-updated\nhttps://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/services/data-lake-analytics/",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 171,
      "original_number": "171",
      "question": "✑ View security recommendations.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Advisor displays security recommendations"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Advisor provides you with"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Marketplace"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Monitor is used to monitor the health of Azure services"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Box 1:\nAzure Monitor is used to monitor the health of Azure services.",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 172,
      "original_number": "172",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYou have an Azure environment. You need to create a new Azure virtual machine from a tablet that runs the Android operating system.\nSolution: You use Bash in Azure Cloud Shell.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nW",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cloud-shell/quickstart https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cloud-shell/overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 173,
      "original_number": "173",
      "question": "You have an on-premises application that sends email noti+cations automatically based on a rule.\nYou plan to migrate the application to Azure.\nYou need to recommend a serverless computing solution for the application.\nWhat should you include in the recommendation?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a web app"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "a server image in Azure Marketplace"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a logic app"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "an API app"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/logic-apps/logic-apps-overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 174,
      "original_number": "174",
      "question": "You plan to deploy a website to Azure. The website will be accessed by users worldwide and will host large video +les.\nYou need to recommend which Azure feature must be used to provide the best video playback experience.\nWhat should you recommend?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "an application gateway"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an Azure ExpressRoute circuit"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a content delivery network (CDN)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "an Azure Trahc Manager pro+le"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nT",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cdn/cdn-overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 175,
      "original_number": "175",
      "question": "Your company plans to deploy several million sensors that will upload data to Azure.\nYou need to identify which Azure resources must be created to support the planned solution.\nWhich two Azure resources should you identify? Each correct answer presents part of the solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Data Lake"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Queue storage"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure File Storage"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure IoT Hub"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "Azure Noti+cation Hubs"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "AD\nI",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/iot-hub/about-iot-hub\nhttps://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/iot-hub/iot-hub-devguide-messages-d2c",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 176,
      "original_number": "176",
      "question": "You have an Azure web app.\nYou need to manage the settings of the web app from an iPhone.\nWhat are two Azure management tools that you can use? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure CLI"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "the Azure portal"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Cloud Shell"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Windows PowerShell"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "Azure Storage Explorer"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "BC\nT",
      "explanation": "http://www.deployazure.com/management/managing-azure-from-ipad/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 177,
      "original_number": "177",
      "question": "Your company plans to deploy an Arti+cial Intelligence (AI) solution in Azure.\nWhat should the company use to build, test, and deploy predictive analytics solutions?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Logic Apps"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Machine Learning Designer"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Batch"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Cosmos DB"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/machine-learning/concept-designer",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 178,
      "original_number": "178",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "No",
        "No"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nAzure Advisor does not generate a list of virtual machines that ARE protected by Azure Backup. Azure Advisor does however, generate a list of\nvirtual that ARE\nNOT protected by Azure Backup. You can view a list of virtual machines that are protected by Azure Backup by viewing the Protected Items in\nthe Azure Recovery\nServices Vault.\nBox 2: No -\nIf you implement the security recommendations, you company's score will increase, not decrease.\nBox 3: No -\nThere is no requirement to implement the security recommendations provided by Azure Advisor. The recommendations are just that,\n'recommendations'. They are not 'requirements'.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Azure Advisor does not generate a list of virtual machines that ARE protected by Azure Backup",
        "If you implement the security recommendations, you company's score will increase, not decrease.",
        "There is no requirement to implement the security recommendations provided by Azure Advisor"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 179,
      "original_number": "179",
      "question": "What can you use to automatically send an alert if an administrator stops an Azure virtual machine?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Advisor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Service Health"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Monitor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Network Watcher"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nR",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-monitor/insights/vminsights-alerts",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 180,
      "original_number": "180",
      "question": "Match the Azure services to the correct descriptions.\nInstructions: To answer, drag the appropriate Azure service from the column on the left to its description on the right. Each service may be used\nonce, more than once, or not at all.\n\nNOTE: Each correct match is worth one point",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/services/synapse-analytics/ https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/machine-learning/overview-what-is-\nazure-ml https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/iot-hub/about-iot-hub https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-functions/functions-\noverview",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 181,
      "original_number": "181",
      "question": "You have an Azure environment.\nYou need to create a new Azure virtual machine from a tablet that runs the Android operating system.\nWhat are three possible solutions? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Use Bash in Azure Cloud Shell."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Use PowerShell in Azure Cloud Shell."
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Use the PowerApps portal."
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Use the Security & Compliance admin center."
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "Use the Azure portal."
        }
      ],
      "answer": "ABE\nT",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 182,
      "original_number": "182",
      "question": "A team of developers at your company plans to deploy, and then remove, 50 virtual machines each week. All the virtual machines are con+gured\nby using Azure\nResource Manager templates.\nYou need to recommend which Azure service will minimize the administrative effort required to deploy and remove the virtual machines.\nWhat should you recommend?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Reserved Virtual Machine (VM) Instances"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure DevTest Labs"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure virtual machine scale sets"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Virtual Desktop"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nD",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/lab-services/devtest-lab-overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 183,
      "original_number": "183",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nAzure Advisor provides you with a consistent, consolidated view of recommendations for all your Azure resources. It integrates with Azure\nSecurity Center to bring you security recommendations. You can get security recommendations from the Security tab on the Advisor dashboard.\nExamples of recommendations include restricting access to virtual machines by con+guring Network Security Groups, enabling storage\nencryption, installing vulnerability assessment solutions.\nHowever, Azure Advisor does not provide recommendations on how to improve the security of an Azure AD environment.\nBox 2: Yes -\n\nAdvisor helps you optimize and reduce your overall Azure spend by identifying idle and underutilized resources. You can get cost\nrecommendations from the Cost tab on the Advisor dashboard.\nBox 3: No.\nAzure Advisor does not provide recommendations on how to con+gure network settings on Azure virtual machines.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Azure Advisor provides you with a consistent, consolidated view of recommendations for all your Azure resources",
        "Advisor helps you optimize and reduce your overall Azure spend by identifying idle and underutilized resources"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 184,
      "original_number": "184",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYou have an Azure subscription named Subscription1. You sign in to the Azure portal and create a resource group named RG1.\nFrom Azure documentation, you have the following command that creates a virtual machine named VM1. az vm create --resource-group RG1 --\nname VM1 --image UbuntuLTS --generate-ssh-keys\nYou need to create VM1 in Subscription1 by using the command.\nSolution: From the Azure portal, launch Azure Cloud Shell and select PowerShell. Run the command in Cloud Shell.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nT",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machines/linux/quick-create-cli",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 185,
      "original_number": "185",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYou have an Azure subscription named Subscription1. You sign in to the Azure portal and create a resource group named RG1.\nFrom Azure documentation, you have the following command that creates a virtual machine named VM1. az vm create --resource-group RG1 --\nname VM1 --image UbuntuLTS\n--generate-ssh-keys\nYou need to create VM1 in Subscription1 by using the command.\nSolution: From a computer that runs Windows 10, install Azure CLI. From PowerShell, sign in to Azure and then run the command.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nT",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/cli/azure/install-azure-cli-windows?view=azure-cli-latest",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 186,
      "original_number": "186",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYou have an Azure subscription named Subscription1. You sign in to the Azure portal and create a resource group named RG1.\nFrom Azure documentation, you have the following command that creates a virtual machine named VM1. az vm create --resource-group RG1 --\nname VM1 --image UbuntuLTS\n--generate-ssh-keys\nYou need to create VM1 in Subscription1 by using the command.\nSolution: From a computer that runs Windows 10, install Azure CLI. From a command prompt, sign in to Azure and then run the command.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nT",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/cli/azure/install-azure-cli-windows?view=azure-cli-latest",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 187,
      "original_number": "187",
      "question": "You have three virtual machines (VMs) that are included in an availability set.\n\nYou try to resize one of the VMs, but you get an error message saying the desired size is not available in the availability set.\n\nYou need to ensure that you can resize the VM.\n\nWhich tool or tools should you use on each computer? To answer, select the appropriate options.\n\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Previously, the Azure CLI (or x-plat CLI) was the only option for managing Azure subscriptions and resources from the command-line on Linux\nand macOS. Now with the open source and cross-platform release of PowerShell, you'll be able to manage all your Azure resources from\nWindows, Linux and macOS using your tool of choice, either the Azure CLI or Azure PowerShell cmdlets.\n\nThe Azure portal runs in a web browser so can be used in either operating system.",
      "questionType": "MATCHING",
      "matchingItems": [
        {
          "item": "Computer1",
          "options": [
            "The Azure CLI and the Azure portal",
            "The Azure portal and Azure PowerShell",
            "The Azure CLI and Azure PowerShell",
            "The Azure CLI, the Azure portal, and Azure PowerShell"
          ],
          "answer": "The Azure CLI and Azure PowerShell"
        },
        {
          "item": "Computer2",
          "options": [
            "The Azure CLI and the Azure portal",
            "The Azure portal and Azure PowerShell",
            "The Azure CLI and Azure PowerShell",
            "The Azure CLI, the Azure portal, and Azure PowerShell"
          ],
          "answer": "The Azure CLI and Azure PowerShell"
        },
        {
          "item": "Computer3",
          "options": [
            "The Azure CLI and the Azure portal",
            "The Azure portal and Azure PowerShell",
            "The Azure CLI and Azure PowerShell",
            "The Azure CLI, the Azure portal, and Azure PowerShell"
          ],
          "answer": "The Azure CLI, the Azure portal, and Azure PowerShell"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 188,
      "original_number": "188",
      "question": "You can access Compliance Manager from the _______",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Active Directory admin center"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure portal"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Microsoft 365 admin center"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Microsoft Service Trust Portal"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 189,
      "original_number": "189",
      "question": "Azure policies are used to de+ne rules for what can be deployed and how it should be deployed. Whilst this can help in ensuring consistency,",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Resource Manager templates provides"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure environment"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure policies are used to de"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure policies do not provide the common platform for deploying objects to"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Azure Resource Manager templates provides a common platform for deploying objects to a cloud infrastructure and for implementing\nconsistency across the\nAzure environment.\nAzure policies are used to de+ne rules for what can be deployed and how it should be deployed. Whilst this can help in ensuring consistency,\nAzure policies do not provide the common platform for deploying objects to a cloud infrastructure.",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 190,
      "original_number": "190",
      "question": "Match the Azure service to the correct description.\nInstructions: To answer, drag the appropriate Azure service from the column on the left to its description on the right. Each service may be used\nonce, more than once, or not at all.\n\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/bot-service/bot-service-overview-introduction?view=azure-bot-service-4.0\nhttps://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/machine-learning/overview-what-is-azure-ml https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-\nfunctions/ https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/iot-hub/about-iot-hub",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 191,
      "original_number": "191",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nAn Azure administrator plans to run a PowerShell script that creates Azure resources.\nYou need to recommend which computer con+guration to use to run the script.\nSolution: Run the script from a computer that runs Windows 10 and has the Azure PowerShell module installed.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nA P",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/powershell/scripting/components/ise/how-to-write-and-run-scripts-in-the-windows-powershell-ise?\nview=powershell-6",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 192,
      "original_number": "192",
      "question": "Match the Azure services to the correct description.\nInstructions: To answer, drag the appropriate Azure service from the column on the left to its description on the right. Each service may be used\nonce, more than once, or not at all.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machines/windows/overview https://docs.microsoft.com/en-\nus/azure/security/fundamentals/paas-applications-using-app-services https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-functions/\nhttps://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/container-instances/container-instances-overview",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 193,
      "original_number": "193",
      "question": "Which service provides serverless computing in Azure?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Virtual Machines"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Functions"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure storage account"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure dedicated hosts"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-functions/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 194,
      "original_number": "194",
      "question": "An Azure administrator plans to run a PowerShell script that creates Azure resources.\nYou need to recommend which computer con+guration to use to run the script.\nWhich three computers can run the script? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a computer that runs macOS and has PowerShell Core 6.0 installed."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "a computer that runs Windows 10 and has the Azure PowerShell module installed."
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a computer that runs Linux and has the Azure PowerShell module installed."
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a computer that runs Linux and has the Azure CLI tools installed."
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "a computer that runs Chrome OS and uses Azure Cloud Shell."
        }
      ],
      "answer": "ABE\nA P",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/powershell/scripting/components/ise/how-to-write-and-run-scripts-in-the-windows-powershell-ise?\nview=powershell-6 https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cloud-shell/quickstart-powershell",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 195,
      "original_number": "195",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYou have an Azure subscription named Subscription1. You sign in to the Azure portal and create a resource group named RG1.\nFrom Azure documentation, you have the following command that creates a virtual machine named VM1. az vm create --resource-group RG1 --\nname VM1 --image UbuntuLTS --generate-ssh-keys\nYou need to create VM1 in Subscription1 by using the command.\nSolution: From the Azure portal, launch Azure Cloud Shell and select Bash. Run the command in Cloud Shell.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nT",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machines/linux/quick-create-cli",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 196,
      "original_number": "196",
      "question": "Your company has several business units.\nEach business unit requires 20 different Azure resources for daily operation. All the business units require the same type of Azure resources.\nYou need to recommend a solution to automate the creation of the Azure resources.\nWhat should you include in the recommendations?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Resource Manager templates"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "virtual machine scale sets"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "the Azure API Management service"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "management groups"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nY",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-resource-manager/templates/overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 197,
      "original_number": "197",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cost-management-billing/costs/quick-acm-cost-analysis https://docs.microsoft.com/en-\nus/azure/cost-management-billing/costs/cost-analysis-common-uses",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 198,
      "original_number": "198",
      "question": "What can you use to identify underutilized or unused Azure virtual machines?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Advisor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Cost Management + Billing"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure reservations"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Policy"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/advisor/advisor-overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 199,
      "original_number": "199",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nWhich node in the Azure portal should you use to assign a user the Reader role for a resource group? To answer, select the node in the answer\narea.\n\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/role-based-access-control/role-assignments-portal",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 200,
      "original_number": "200",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/databricks/",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 201,
      "original_number": "201",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "Yes",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: Yes -\nBox 2: No -\nCloud services can be managed through https://portal.azure.com/\nIn the Cloud Services area of the Azure portal, you can:\nUpdate a service role or a deployment.\nPromote a staged deployment to production.\nLink resources to your cloud service so that you can see the resource dependencies and scale the resources together.\nDelete a cloud service or a deployment.\nBox 3: Yes -",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Box 2: No -\nCloud services can be managed through https://portal.azure.com/\nIn the Cloud Services area of the Azure portal, you can:\nUpdate a service role or a deployment",
        "Reference:\nhttps://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cloud-services/cloud-services-how-to-manage-portal"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 202,
      "original_number": "202",
      "question": "Match the Azure service to the correct de+nition.\nInstructions: To answer, drag the appropriate Azure service from the column on the left to its description on the right. Each service may be used\nonce, more than once, or not at all.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-functions/\nhttps://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-databricks/what-is-azure-databricks#apache-spark-based-analytics-platform\nhttps://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-monitor/app/app-insights-overview https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/app-\nservice/overview",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 203,
      "original_number": "203",
      "question": "A team of developers at your company plans to deploy, and then remove, 50 customized virtual machines each week. Thirty of the virtual\nmachines run Windows\nServer 2016 and 20 of the virtual machines run Ubuntu Linux.\nYou need to recommend which Azure service will minimize the administrative effort required to deploy and remove the virtual machines.\nWhat should you recommend?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Reserved Virtual Machines (VM) Instances"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure virtual machine scale sets"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure DevTest Labs"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Microsoft Managed Desktop"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nD",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/lab-services/devtest-lab-overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 204,
      "original_number": "204",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements select Yes if the statement is true Otherwise select No\n\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "Y",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/powershell/azure/what-is-azure-powershell?view=azps-6.6.0\nhttps://serverfault.com/",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 205,
      "original_number": "205",
      "question": "A support engineer plans to perform several Azure management tasks by using the Azure CLI.\nYou install the CLI on a computer.\nYou need to tell the support engineer which tools to use to run the CLI.\nWhich two tools should you instruct the support engineer to use? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Command Prompt"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Resource Explorer"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Windows PowerShell"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Windows Defender Firewall"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "Network and Sharing Center"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "AC\nF",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/cli/azure/install-azure-cli-windows?view=azure-cli-latest",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 206,
      "original_number": "206",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYou have an Azure environment. You need to create a new Azure virtual machine from a tablet that runs the Android operating system.\nSolution: You use PowerShell in Azure Cloud Shell.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cloud-shell/features",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 207,
      "original_number": "207",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYou have an Azure environment. You need to create a new Azure virtual machine from a tablet that runs the Android operating system.\nSolution: You use the PowerApps portal.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nP",
      "explanation": "https://powerapps.microsoft.com/en-us/blog/introducing-powerapps-portals-powerful-low-code-websites-for-external-users/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 208,
      "original_number": "208",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYou have an Azure environment. You need to create a new Azure virtual machine from a tablet that runs the Android operating system.\nSolution: You use the Azure portal.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nT",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-portal/azure-portal-overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 209,
      "original_number": "209",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "M",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-365/compliance/microsoft-365-compliance-center",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 210,
      "original_number": "210",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-arc/overview",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 211,
      "original_number": "211",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "Yes",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nEasily manage your Azure storage accounts in the cloud, from Windows, macOS, or Linux, using Azure Storage Explorer.\nBox 2: Yes -\nAzure cloud services can be managed in Azure Automation by using the PowerShell cmdlets that are available in the Azure PowerShell tools.\nBox 3: Yes -",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Easily manage your Azure storage accounts in the cloud, from Windows, macOS, or Linux, using Azure Storage Explorer.",
        "Azure cloud services can be managed in Azure Automation by using the PowerShell cmdlets that are available in the Azure PowerShell tools.",
        "Reference:\nhttps://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/features/storage-explorer/\nhttps://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cloud-services/automation-manage-cloud-services"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 212,
      "original_number": "212",
      "question": "Azure Databricks is an Apache Spark-based analytics platform. The platform consists of several components including Machine Learning library. You want to use Databricks machine learning library to _______",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "train a machine learning model"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "implement linear algebra"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "implement computer vision"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "run SQL queries"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Azure Databricks is an Apache Spark-based analytics platform. The platform consists of several components including 'MLib'. Mlib is a\nMachine Learning library consisting of common learning algorithms and utilities, including classi+cation, regression, clustering, collaborative\n+ltering, dimensionality reduction, as well as underlying optimization primitives.",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 213,
      "original_number": "213",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "Yes",
        "Yes",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: Yes -\nAzure Monitor maximizes the availability and performance of your applications and services by delivering a comprehensive solution for\ncollecting, analyzing, and acting on telemetry from your cloud and on-premises environments.\nBox 2: Yes -\nAlerts in Azure Monitor proactively notify you of critical conditions and potentially attempt to take corrective action.\nBox 3: Yes -\nAzure Monitor uses Target Resource, which is the scope and signals available for alerting. A target can be any Azure resource. Example targets:\na virtual machine, a storage account, a virtual machine scale set, a Log Analytics workspace, or an Application Insights resource.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Azure Monitor maximizes the availability and performance of your applications and services by delivering a comprehensive solution for\ncollecting, analyzing, and acting on telemetry from your cloud and",
        "Alerts in Azure Monitor proactively notify you of critical conditions and potentially attempt to take corrective action.",
        "Azure Monitor uses Target Resource, which is the scope and signals available for alerting"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 214,
      "original_number": "214",
      "question": "Which Azure service provides a set of version control tools to manage code?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Repos"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure DevTest Labs"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Storage"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Cosmos DB"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/devops/repos/get-started/what-is-repos?view=azure-devops",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 215,
      "original_number": "215",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nYou need to manage Azure by using Azure Cloud Shell.\nWhich Azure portal icon should you select? To answer, select the appropriate icon in the answer area.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "Y",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cloud-shell/overview?view=azure-cli-latest",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 216,
      "original_number": "216",
      "question": "You have a virtual machine named VM1 that runs Windows Server 2016. VM1 is in the East US Azure region.\nWhich Azure service should you use from the Azure portal to view service failure noti+cations that can affect the availability of VM1?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Service Fabric"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Monitor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure virtual machines"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Advisor"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nI",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machines/maintenance-and-updates",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 217,
      "original_number": "217",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYour Azure environment contains multiple Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to ensure that a virtual machine named VM1 is accessible from the Internet over HTTP.\nSolution: You modify an Azure Trahc Manager pro+le.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/trahc-manager/trahc-manager-overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 218,
      "original_number": "218",
      "question": "Your company plans to deploy several web servers and several database servers to Azure.\nYou need to recommend an Azure solution to limit the types of connections from the web servers to the database servers.\nWhat should you include in the recommendation?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "network security groups (NSGs)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Service Bus"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a local network gateway"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a route +lter"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-network/security-overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 219,
      "original_number": "219",
      "question": "You can use Azure Activity Log to view which user turned off a specific virtual machine during the last 14 days _______",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "You would use the Azure Activity Log, not Access Control to view which user turned off a speci+c virtual machine during the last 14 days.\nActivity logs are kept for 90 days. You can query for any range of dates, as long as the starting date isn't more than 90 days in the past.\nIn this question, we would create a +lter to display shutdown operations on the virtual machine in the last 14 days.",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 220,
      "original_number": "220",
      "question": "Which service provides network trahc +ltering across multiple Azure subscriptions and virtual networks?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Firewall"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an application security group"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure DDoS protection"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a network security group (NSG)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nY",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/+rewall/overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 221,
      "original_number": "221",
      "question": "Which Azure service should you use to store certi+cates?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Security Center"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an Azure Storage account"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Key Vault"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Information Protection"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/key-vault/key-vault-overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 222,
      "original_number": "222",
      "question": "Which Azure service can you use as a security information and event management (SIEM) solution?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Analysis Services"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Sentinel"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Information Protection"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Cognitive Services"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nR",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-in/services/azure-sentinel/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 223,
      "original_number": "223",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/sentinel/overview",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 224,
      "original_number": "224",
      "question": "Match the Azure Services service to the correct descriptions.\nInstructions: To answer, drag the appropriate service from the column on the left to its description on the right. Each service may be used once,\nmore than once, or not at all.\nNOTE: Each correct match is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "I",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/sentinel/overview\nhttps://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/security-center/secure-score-security-controls https://practical365.com/securing-sensitive-\ninformation-in-azure-functions-with-the-azure-key-vault/ https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/active-directory/fundamentals/active-\ndirectory-whatis https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/lighthouse/overview",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 225,
      "original_number": "225",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "No",
        "No"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nAzure +rewall does not encrypt network trahc. It is used to block or allow trahc based on source/destination IP address, source/destination\nports and protocol.\n\nBox 2: No -\nA network security group does not encrypt network trahc. It works in a similar way to a +rewall in that it is used to block or allow trahc based\non source/ destination IP address, source/destination ports and protocol.\nBox 3: No -\nThe question is rather vague as it would depend on the con+guration of the host on the Internet. Windows Server does come with a VPN client\nand it also supports other encryption methods such IPSec encryption or SSL/TLS so it could encrypt the trahc if the Internet host was\ncon+gured to require or accept the encryption.\nHowever, the VM could not encrypt the trahc to an Internet host that is not con+gured to require the encryption.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Azure +rewall does not encrypt network trahc",
        "A network security group does not encrypt network trahc",
        "The question is rather vague as it would depend on the con+guration of the host on the Internet"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 226,
      "original_number": "226",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "Yes",
        "No",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: Yes -\nAzure Security Center is a uni+ed infrastructure security management system that strengthens the security posture of your data centers, and\nprovides advanced threat protection across your hybrid workloads in the cloud - whether they're in Azure or not - as well as on premises.\nBox 2: No -\nOnly two features: Continuous assessment and security recommendations, and Azure secure score, are free.\nBox 3: Yes -\nThe advanced monitoring capabilities in Security Center also let you track and manage compliance and governance over time. The overall\ncompliance provides you with a measure of how much your subscriptions are compliant with policies associated with your workload.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Azure Security Center is a uni+ed infrastructure security management system that strengthens the security posture of your data centers, and\nprovides advanced threat protection across your hybrid workl",
        "Only two features: Continuous assessment and security recommendations, and Azure secure score, are free.",
        "The advanced monitoring capabilities in Security Center also let you track and manage compliance and governance over time"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 227,
      "original_number": "227",
      "question": "You need to complete the defense-in-depth strategy used in a datacenter.\nWhat should you do? To answer, drag the appropriate layers to the correct positions in the model. Each layer may be used once, more than once,\nor not at all.\nYou may need to drag the split bar between panes or scroll to view content.\n\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "https://github.com/undergroundwires/Azure-in-bullet-points/blob/master/AZ-\n900%20Microsoft%20Azure%20Fundamentals/4.2.%20Defence%20in%20Depth.md",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 228,
      "original_number": "228",
      "question": "You have an Azure virtual machine named VM1.\nYou plan to encrypt VM1 by using Azure Disk Encryption.\nWhich Azure resource must you create +rst?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "an Azure Storage account"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an Azure Key Vault"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "an Azure Information Protection policy"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "an Encryption key"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-machines/windows/disk-encryption-overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 229,
      "original_number": "229",
      "question": "Which resources can be used as a source for a Network security group inbound security rule?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Service Tags only"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "IP Addresses, Service tags and Application security groups"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Application security groups only"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "IP Addresses only"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nS",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-network/network-security-groups-overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 230,
      "original_number": "230",
      "question": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/sentinel/tutorial-respond-threats-playbook _______",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Option A (확인 필요)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Option B (확인 필요)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Option C (확인 필요)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Option D (확인 필요)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Reference:\nhttps://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/sentinel/tutorial-respond-threats-playbook",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 231,
      "original_number": "231",
      "question": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/+rewall/tutorial-+rewall-dnat-policy _______",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Option A (확인 필요)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Option B (확인 필요)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Option C (확인 필요)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Option D (확인 필요)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Reference:\nhttps://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/+rewall/tutorial-+rewall-dnat-policy",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 232,
      "original_number": "232",
      "question": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/ddos-protection/ddos-protection-overview _______",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Option A (확인 필요)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Option B (확인 필요)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Option C (확인 필요)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Option D (확인 필요)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Reference:\nhttps://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/ddos-protection/ddos-protection-overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 233,
      "original_number": "233",
      "question": "You have an Azure Sentinel workspace.\nYou need to automate responses to threats detected by Azure Sentinel.\nWhat should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "adaptive network hardening in Azure Security Center"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Service Health"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Monitor workbooks"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "adaptive application controls in Azure Security Center"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 234,
      "original_number": "234",
      "question": "Match the Azure services bene+ts to the correct descriptions.\nInstructions: To answer, drag the appropriate bene+t from the column on the left to its description on the right. Each bene+t may be used once,\nmore than once, or not at all.\nNOTE: Each correct match is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/sentinel/overview\nhttps://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/defender-for-cloud/secure-score-access-and-track https://levelup.gitconnected.com/a-secure-way-to-\nuse-credentials-and-secrets-in-azure-functions-7ec91813c807",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 235,
      "original_number": "235",
      "question": "Which Azure service can you use as a security information and event management (SIEM) solution?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Analysis Services"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Microsoft Sentinel"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Information Protection"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Cognitive Services"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nM",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/sentinel/overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 236,
      "original_number": "236",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/defender-for-cloud/security-policy-concept",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 237,
      "original_number": "237",
      "question": "You have an Azure subscription.\nYou need to review your secure score.\nWhat should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Monitor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Advisor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Help + support"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Microsoft Defender for Cloud"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nT",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/defender-for-cloud/secure-score-security-controls",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 238,
      "original_number": "238",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/defender-for-cloud/just-in-time-access-usage",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 239,
      "original_number": "239",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/defender-for-cloud/regulatory-compliance-dashboard",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 240,
      "original_number": "240",
      "question": "You need to collect and automatically analyze security events from Azure Active Directory (Azure AD).\nWhat should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Microsoft Sentinel"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Synapse Analytics"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure AD Connect"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Key Vault"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nM",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/sentinel/overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 241,
      "original_number": "241",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/active-directory/manage-apps/add-application-portal-setup-sso",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 242,
      "original_number": "242",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "Yes",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nAzure creates the default rules in each network security group that you create. These rules allow some trahc.\nBox 2: Yes -\nA network security group contains zero, or as many rules as desired. These rules can refer to application security groups.\nBox 3: Yes -\nAzure creates the Inbound and OutBound default rules in each network security group that you create.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Azure creates the default rules in each network security group that you create",
        "A network security group contains zero, or as many rules as desired",
        "Azure creates the Inbound and OutBound default rules in each network security group that you create."
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 243,
      "original_number": "243",
      "question": "Match the term to the appropriate description.\nTo answer, drag the appropriate term from the column on the left to its description on the right. Each term may be used once, more than once, or\nnot at all.\nNOTE: Each correct match is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 244,
      "original_number": "244",
      "question": "Your company plans to automate the deployment of servers to Azure.\nYour manager is concerned that you may expose administrative credentials during the deployment.\nYou need to recommend an Azure solution that encrypts the administrative credentials during the deployment.\nWhat should you include in the recommendation?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Key Vault"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Information Protection"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Microsoft Defender for Cloud"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/key-vault/general/security-features",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 245,
      "original_number": "245",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-network/network-security-groups-overview",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 246,
      "original_number": "246",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/services/ddos-protection",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 247,
      "original_number": "247",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/sentinel/tutorial-respond-threats-playbook",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 248,
      "original_number": "248",
      "question": "You need to con+gure an Azure solution that meets the following requirements:\n✑ Secures websites from attacks\n✑ Generates reports that contain details of attempted attacks\nWhat should you include in the solution?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Firewall"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "a network security group (NSG)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Information Protection"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "DDoS protection"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nDD",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/security/fundamentals/ddos-best-practices",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 249,
      "original_number": "249",
      "question": "You need to configure security features for your Azure subscription.\n\nWhich Azure service should you use? To answer, select the appropriate options.\n\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Box 1:\nTo monitor threats by using sensors, you would use Azure Advanced Threat Protection (ATP).\nAzure Advanced Threat Protection (ATP) is a cloud-based security solution that leverages your on-premises Active Directory signals to identify,\ndetect, and investigate advanced threats, compromised identities, and malicious insider actions directed at your organization.\nSensors are software packages you install on your servers to upload information to Azure ATP.\nBox 2:\nTo enforce MFA based on a condition, you would use Azure Active Directory Identity Protection.\nAzure AD Identity Protection helps you manage the roll-out of Azure Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA) registration by con+guring a Conditional\nAccess policy to require MFA registration no matter what modern authentication app you are signing in to.",
      "questionType": "MATCHING",
      "matchingItems": [
        {
          "item": "Monitor threats by using sensors",
          "options": [
            "Azure Monitor",
            "Azure Security Center",
            "Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) Identity Protection",
            "Azure Advanced Threat Protection (ATP)"
          ],
          "answer": "Azure Advanced Threat Protection (ATP)"
        },
        {
          "item": "Enforce Azure MFA based on a condition",
          "options": [
            "Azure Monitor",
            "Azure Security Center",
            "Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) Identity Protection",
            "Azure Advanced Threat Protection (ATP)"
          ],
          "answer": "Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) Identity Protection"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 250,
      "original_number": "250",
      "question": "Your Azure environment contains multiple Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to ensure that a virtual machine named VM1 is accessible from the Internet over HTTP.\nWhat are two possible solutions? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Modify an Azure Trahc Manager pro+le"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Modify a network security group (NSG)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Modify a DDoS protection plan"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Modify an Azure +rewall"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-network/security-overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 251,
      "original_number": "251",
      "question": "You can enable just-in-time (JIT) VM access by using _______",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Bastion"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Firewall"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Front Door"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Security Center"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "The just-in-time (JIT) virtual machine (VM) access feature in Azure Security Center allows you to lock down inbound trahc to your Azure Virtual\nMachines. This reduces exposure to attacks while providing easy access when you need to connect to a VM.",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 252,
      "original_number": "252",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-network/network-security-group-how-it-works",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 253,
      "original_number": "253",
      "question": "You have an Azure environment that contains 10 virtual networks and 100 virtual machines.\nYou need to limit the amount of inbound trahc to all the Azure virtual networks.\nWhat should you create?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "one application security group (ASG)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "10 virtual network gateways"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "10 Azure ExpressRoute circuits"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "one Azure +rewall"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nY",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/+rewall/overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 254,
      "original_number": "254",
      "question": "This question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.\nAzure Key Vault is used to store secrets for Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) user accounts.\nInstructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed`. If the statement is incorrect, select the\nanswer choice that makes the statement correct.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "No change is needed"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) administrative accounts"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Personally Identi+able Information (PII)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "server applications"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nK",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/modules/manage-secrets-with-azure-key-vault/2-what-is-key-vault https://docs.microsoft.com/en-\nus/azure/key-vault/key-vault-overview https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/modules/manage-secrets-with-azure-key-vault/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 255,
      "original_number": "255",
      "question": "Your company plans to automate the deployment of servers to Azure.\nYour manager is concerned that you may expose administrative credentials during the deployment.\nYou need to recommend an Azure solution that encrypts the administrative credentials during the deployment.\nWhat should you include in the recommendation?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Key Vault"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Information Protection"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Security Center"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/key-vault/key-vault-overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 256,
      "original_number": "256",
      "question": "You plan to deploy several Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to control the ports that devices on the Internet can use to access the virtual machines.\nWhat should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a network security group (NSG)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) role"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "an Azure Active Directory group"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "an Azure key vault"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-network/security-overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 257,
      "original_number": "257",
      "question": "A network security group works like a +rewall. You can attach a network security group to a virtual network and/or individual subnets within the",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure resources"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure resources in an Azure virtual network with"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "When you create a virtual machine, the default setting is to create a Network Security Group attached to the network interface assigned to a\nvirtual machine.\nA network security group works like a +rewall. You can attach a network security group to a virtual network and/or individual subnets within the\nvirtual network.\nYou can also attach a network security group to a network interface assigned to a virtual machine. You can use multiple network security\ngroups within a virtual network to restrict",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 258,
      "original_number": "258",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/role-based-access-control/built-in-roles#owner",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 259,
      "original_number": "259",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYour Azure environment contains multiple Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to ensure that a virtual machine named VM1 is accessible from the Internet over HTTP.\nSolution: You modify a network security group (NSG).\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-network/security-overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 260,
      "original_number": "260",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYour Azure environment contains multiple Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to ensure that a virtual machine named VM1 is accessible from the Internet over HTTP.\nSolution: You modify a DDoS protection plan.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nDD",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/virtual-network/ddos-protection-overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 261,
      "original_number": "261",
      "question": "You need to collect and automatically analyze security events from Azure Active Directory (Azure AD).\nWhat should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Sentinel"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Synapse Analytics"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure AD Connect"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Key Vault"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nR",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/sentinel/overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 262,
      "original_number": "262",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYour Azure environment contains multiple Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to ensure that a virtual machine named VM1 is accessible from the Internet over HTTP.\nSolution: You modify an Azure +rewall.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/+rewall/overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 263,
      "original_number": "263",
      "question": "This question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.\nAzure Germany can be used by legal residents of Germany only.\nInstructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed`. If the statement is incorrect, select the\nanswer choice that makes the statement correct.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "no change is needed"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "only enterprises that are registered in Germany"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "only enterprises that purchase their azure licenses from a partner based in Germany"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "any user or enterprise that requires its data to reside in Germany"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/germany/germany-welcome?toc=%2fazure%2fgermany%2ftoc.json https://docs.microsoft.com/en-\nus/azure/germany/germany-overview-data-trustee",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 264,
      "original_number": "264",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "Yes",
        "Yes",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: Yes -\nThe tool you would use to sync the accounts is Azure AD Connect. The Azure Active Directory Connect synchronization services (Azure AD\nConnect sync) is a main component of Azure AD Connect. It takes care of all the operations that are related to synchronize identity data\nbetween your on-premises environment and\nAzure AD.\nBox 2: Yes -\nAs described above, third-party cloud services and on-premises Active Directory can be used to access Azure resources. This is known as\n'federation'.\nFederation is a collection of domains that have established trust. The level of trust may vary, but typically includes authentication and almost\nalways includes authorization. A typical federation might include a number of organizations that have established trust for shared access to a\nset of resources.\nBox 3: Yes -\n\nAzure Active Directory (Azure AD) is a centralized identity provider in the cloud. This is the primary built-in authentication and authorization\nservice to provide secure access to ",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "The tool you would use to sync the accounts is Azure AD Connect",
        "As described above, third-party cloud services and on-premises Active Directory can be used to access Azure resources",
        "Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) is a centralized identity provider in the cloud"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 265,
      "original_number": "265",
      "question": "You can view your company's regulatory compliance report from _______",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Advisor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Analysis Services"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Monitor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Security Center"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D",
      "explanation": "The advanced monitoring capabilities in Security Center lets you track and manage compliance and governance over time. The overall\ncompliance provides you with a measure of how much your subscriptions are compliant with policies associated with your workload.",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 266,
      "original_number": "266",
      "question": "What should you use to evaluate whether your company's Azure environment meets regulatory requirements?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Service Health"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Knowledge Center"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Security Center"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Advisor"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nT",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/security-center/security-center-intro",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 267,
      "original_number": "267",
      "question": "Azure Information Protection is used to automatically add a watermark to Microsoft Word documents that contain credit card information.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Information Protection is used to automatically add"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Information Protection labels to apply classi"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Azure Information Protection is used to automatically add a watermark to Microsoft Word documents that contain credit card information.\nYou use Azure Information Protection labels to apply classi+cation to documents and emails. When you do this, the classi+cation is identi+able\nregardless of where the data is stored or with whom it's shared. The labels can include visual markings such as a header, footer, or watermark.\nLabels can be applied automatically by administrators who de+ne rules and con",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 268,
      "original_number": "268",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "Yes",
        "No"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nAzure Active Directory (Azure AD) is a cloud-based service. It does not require domain controllers on virtual machines.\nBox 2: Yes -\nAzure Active Directory (Azure AD) is a centralized identity provider in the cloud. This is the primary built-in authentication and authorization\nservice to provide secure access to Azure resources and Microsoft 365.\nBox 3: No -\nUser accounts in Azure Active Directory can be assigned multiple licenses for different Azure or Microsoft 365 services.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) is a cloud-based service",
        "Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) is a centralized identity provider in the cloud",
        "User accounts in Azure Active Directory can be assigned multiple licenses for different Azure or Microsoft 365 services."
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 269,
      "original_number": "269",
      "question": "Which two types of customers are eligible to use Azure Government to develop a cloud solution? Each correct answer presents a complete\nsolution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a Canadian government contractor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "a European government contractor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a United States government entity"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a United States government contractor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "a European government entity"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "CD\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/modules/intro-to-azure-government/2-what-is-azure-government",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 270,
      "original_number": "270",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "No"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nIt is not true that you must deploy a federation solution or sync on-premises identities to the cloud. You can have a cloud-only environment and\nuse MFA.\nBox 2: No -\nPicture identi+cation and passport numbers are not valid MFA authentication methods. Valid methods include: Password, Microsoft\nAuthenticator App, SMS and\nVoice call.\nBox 3:\nYou can con+gure MFA to be required for administrator accounts only or you can con+gure MFA for any user account.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "It is not true that you must deploy a federation solution or sync on-premises identities to the cloud",
        "Picture identi+cation and passport numbers are not valid MFA authentication methods"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 271,
      "original_number": "271",
      "question": "You need to ensure that when Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) users connect to Azure AD from the Internet by using an anonymous IP address,\nthe users are prompted automatically to change their password.\nWhich Azure service should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure AD Connect Health"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure AD Privileged Identity Management"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Advanced Threat Protection (ATP)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure AD Identity Protection"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/active-directory/identity-protection/howto-sign-in-risk-policy https://docs.microsoft.com/en-\nus/azure/active-directory/identity-protection/concept-identity-protection-risks",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 272,
      "original_number": "272",
      "question": "Match the term to the correct de+nition.\nInstructions: To answer, drag the appropriate term from the column on the left to its description on the right. Each term may be used once, more\nthan once, or not at all.\n\nNOTE: Each correct match is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/National_Institute_of_Standards_and_Technology\nhttps://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/General_Data_Protection_Regulation https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-government/documentation-\ngovernment-welcome",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 273,
      "original_number": "273",
      "question": "To what should an application connect to retrieve security tokens?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "an Azure Storage account"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a certi+cate store"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "an Azure key vault"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nK",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/modules/manage-secrets-with-azure-key-vault/2-what-is-key-vault https://docs.microsoft.com/en-\nus/azure/key-vault/key-vault-overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 274,
      "original_number": "274",
      "question": "Your network contains an Active Directory forest. The forest contains 5,000 user accounts.\nYour company plans to migrate all network resources to Azure and to decommission the on-premises data center.\nYou need to recommend a solution to minimize the impact on users after the planned migration.\nWhat should you recommend?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Implement Azure Multi-Factor Authentication (MFA)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Sync all the Active Directory user accounts to Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Instruct all users to change their password"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Create a guest user account in Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) for each user"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nT",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/active-directory/hybrid/how-to-connect-sync-whatis",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 275,
      "original_number": "275",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "Yes",
        "Yes",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: Yes -\nYou can send Azure AD activity logs to Azure Monitor logs to enable rich visualizations, monitoring and alerting on the connected data.\nAll data collected by Azure Monitor +ts into one of two fundamental types, metrics and logs (including Azure AD activity logs). Activity logs\nrecord when resources are created or modi+ed. Metrics tell you how the resource is performing and the resources that it's consuming.\nBox 2: Yes -\nAzure Monitor can consolidate log entries from multiple Azure resources, subscriptions, and tenants into one location for analysis together.\nBox 3: Yes -\nYou can create alerts in Azure Monitor.\nAlerts in Azure Monitor proactively notify you of critical conditions and potentially attempt to take corrective action. Alert rules based on\nmetrics provide near real time alerting based on numeric values, while rules based on logs allow for complex logic across data from multiple\nsources.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "You can send Azure AD activity logs to Azure Monitor logs to enable rich visualizations, monitoring and alerting on the connected data",
        "Azure Monitor can consolidate log entries from multiple Azure resources, subscriptions, and tenants into one location for analysis together.",
        "You can create alerts in Azure Monitor"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 276,
      "original_number": "276",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nYou create a resource group named RG1 in Azure Resource Manager.\nYou need to prevent the accidental deletion of the resources in RG1.\n\nWhich setting should you use? To answer, select the appropriate setting in the answer area.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "Y",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-resource-manager/resource-group-lock-resources",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 277,
      "original_number": "277",
      "question": "You have a resource group named RG1.\nYou need to prevent the creation of virtual machines in RG1. The solution must ensure that other objects can be created in RG1.\nWhat should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a lock"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an Azure role"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a tag"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "an Azure policy"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/governance/policy/overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 278,
      "original_number": "278",
      "question": "You have an Azure subscription and 100 Windows 10 devices.\nYou need to ensure that only users whose devices have the latest security patches installed can access Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)-\nintegrated applications.\nWhat should you implement?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a conditional access policy"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Bastion"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Firewall"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Policy"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nR",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/active-directory/conditional-access/concept-conditional-access-policies",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 279,
      "original_number": "279",
      "question": "What can Azure Information Protection encrypt?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "network trahc"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "documents and email messages"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "an Azure Storage account"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "an Azure SQL database"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/information-protection/what-is-information-protection https://docs.microsoft.com/en-\nus/azure/information-protection/quickstart-label-dnf-protectedemail",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 280,
      "original_number": "280",
      "question": "What should you use to evaluate whether your company's Azure environment meets regulatory requirements?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "the Knowledge Center website"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "the Advisor blade from the Azure portal"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Compliance Manager from the Service Trust Portal"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "the Solutions blade from the Azure portal"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nC",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-365/compliance/get-started-with-service-trust-portal?view=o365-worldwide",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 281,
      "original_number": "281",
      "question": "An Azure service is available to all Azure customers when it is in _______",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "public preview"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "private preview"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "development"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "an Enterprise Agreement (EA) subscription"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 282,
      "original_number": "282",
      "question": "You have an Azure subscription.\nWhere will you +nd details on the personal data collected by Microsoft, how Microsoft uses the data, and what the data is used for?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "the Data Protection Addendum"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "the Microsoft Online Services Terms"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "the Microsoft Privacy Statement"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Security Center"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nT",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/support/legal/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 283,
      "original_number": "283",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/active-directory/fundamentals/active-directory-whatis https://docs.microsoft.com/en-\nus/azure/active-directory/manage-apps/what-is-single-sign-on https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/active-directory/devices/concept-\nazure-ad-register",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 284,
      "original_number": "284",
      "question": "The VNet will be marked as 'Non-compliant' when the policy is assigned. However, it will not be deleted and will continue to function normally.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Policy is"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure that you use to create"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "The VNet will be marked as 'Non-compliant' when the policy is assigned. However, it will not be deleted and will continue to function normally.\nAzure Policy is a service in Azure that you use to create, assign, and manage policies. These policies enforce different rules and effects over\nyour resources, so those resources stay compliant with your corporate standards and service level agreements.\nIf there are any existing resources that aren't compliant with a new policy assignment, they appear un",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 285,
      "original_number": "285",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://www.microsoft.com/en-us/trust-center",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 286,
      "original_number": "286",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "Yes",
        "Yes",
        "No"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: Yes -\nYou use Azure Policy to enforce tagging rules and conventions.\nBox 2: Yes -\nEach resource or resource group can have a maximum of 50 tags.\nBox 3: No -\nTags applied to the resource group or subscription aren't inherited by the resources.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "You use Azure Policy to enforce tagging rules and conventions.",
        "Each resource or resource group can have a maximum of 50 tags.",
        "Tags applied to the resource group or subscription aren't inherited by the resources."
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 287,
      "original_number": "287",
      "question": "Match the resources to the appropriate descriptions.\nTo answer, drag the appropriate resource from the column on the left to its description on the right. Each resource may be used once, more than\nonce, or not at all.\nNOTE: Each correct match is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/support/legal/",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 288,
      "original_number": "288",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/active-directory/authentication/concept-mfa-howitworks",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 289,
      "original_number": "289",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://support.azure.cn/en-us/support/faq/",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 290,
      "original_number": "290",
      "question": "What should you use to evaluate whether your company's Azure environment meets regulatory requirements?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Service Health"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Knowledge Center"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Microsoft Defender for Cloud"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Advisor"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nM",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/defender-for-cloud/regulatory-compliance-dashboard",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 291,
      "original_number": "291",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "M",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-365/compliance/get-started-with-service-trust-portal",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 292,
      "original_number": "292",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-365/compliance/get-started-with-service-trust-portal?view=o365-worldwide",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 293,
      "original_number": "293",
      "question": "Your company has an Azure subscription that contains resources in several regions.\nYou need to create the Azure resource that must be used to meet the policy requirement.\nWhat should you create?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a read-only lock"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "an Azure policy"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a management group"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a reservation"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/governance/policy/overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 294,
      "original_number": "294",
      "question": "This question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.\nFrom Azure Cloud Shell, you can track your company's regulatory standards and regulations, such as ISO 27001.\nInstructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed.` If the statement is incorrect, select the\nanswer choice that makes the statement correct.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "No change is needed."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "the Microsoft Cloud Partner Portal"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Compliance Manager"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "the Trust Center"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nM",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-365/compliance/compliance-manager-overview https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cloud-\nshell/overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 295,
      "original_number": "295",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/active-directory-domain-services/manage-group-policy https://docs.microsoft.com/en-\nus/azure/active-directory/devices/azureadjoin-plan",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 296,
      "original_number": "296",
      "question": "The Microsoft Privacy Statement explains what personal data Microsoft processes, how Microsoft processes the data, and _______",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "the purposes for processing the data"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "how to contact Microsoft"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "how to request deletion of the data"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "the retention period for the data"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "The Microsoft Privacy Statement explains what personal data Microsoft processes, how Microsoft processes the data, and the purpose of\nprocessing the data",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 297,
      "original_number": "297",
      "question": "Authentication is the process of verifying a user's _______",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "credentials"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "authorization"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "access level"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "role"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Authentication, not authorization is the process of verifying a user's credentials.\nThe difference between authentication and authorization is:\n✑ Authentication is proving your identity, proving that you are who you say you are. The most common example of this is logging in to a system\nby providing credentials such as a username and password.\n✑ Authorization is what you're allowed to do once you've been authenticated. For example, what resources you're allowed to access and what\nyou can do with those resources.",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 298,
      "original_number": "298",
      "question": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/governance/policy/overview _______",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Option A (확인 필요)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Option B (확인 필요)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Option C (확인 필요)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Option D (확인 필요)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Reference:\nhttps://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/governance/policy/overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 299,
      "original_number": "299",
      "question": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/governance/policy/overview _______",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Option A (확인 필요)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Option B (확인 필요)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Option C (확인 필요)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Option D (확인 필요)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Reference:\nhttps://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/governance/policy/overview",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 300,
      "original_number": "300",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/blog/new-capabilities-to-enable-robust-gdpr-compliance/",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 301,
      "original_number": "301",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/governance/blueprints/overview",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 302,
      "original_number": "302",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/china/overview-operations https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-\ngovernment/documentation-government-welcome",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 303,
      "original_number": "303",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-resource-manager/management/lock-resources",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 304,
      "original_number": "304",
      "question": "Your company plans to migrate all on-premises data to Azure.\nYou need to identify whether Azure complies with the company's regional requirements.\nWhat should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "the Knowledge Center"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Marketplace"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "the MyApps portal"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "the Trust Center"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nA",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/overview/trusted-cloud/compliance/ https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-365/compliance/get-\nstarted-with-service-trust-portal",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 305,
      "original_number": "305",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "Yes",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nAuthorization to access Azure resources can be provided by other identity providers by using federation. A commonly used example of this is to\nfederate your on- premises Active Directory environment with Azure AD and use this federation for authentication and authorization.\nBox 2: Yes -\nAs described above, third-party cloud services and on-premises Active Directory can be used to access Azure resources. This is known as\n'federation'.\nFederation is a collection of domains that have established trust. The level of trust may vary, but typically includes authentication and almost\nalways includes authorization. A typical federation might include a number of organizations that have established trust for shared access to a\nset of resources.\nBox 3: Yes -\nAzure Active Directory (Azure AD) is a centralized identity provider in the cloud. This is the primary built-in authentication and authorization\nservice to provide secure access to Azure resources.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Authorization to access Azure resources can be provided by other identity providers by using federation",
        "As described above, third-party cloud services and on-premises Active Directory can be used to access Azure resources",
        "Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) is a centralized identity provider in the cloud"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 306,
      "original_number": "306",
      "question": "You can configure a lock on a resource group to prevent the accidental deletion of the resource group _______",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "You can con+gure a lock on a resource group to prevent the accidental deletion of the resource group. The lock applies to everyone, including\nglobal administrators. If you want to delete the resource group, the lock must be removed +rst.\nAs an administrator, you may need to lock a subscription, resource group, or resource to prevent other users in your organization from\naccidentally deleting or modifying critical resources. You can set the lock level to CanNotDelete or ReadOnly. In the portal, the locks are called\nDelete and Read-only respectively.\n✑ CanNotDelete means authorized users can still read and modify a resource, but they can't delete the resource.\nReadOnly means authorized users can read a resource, but they can't delete or update the resource. Applying this lock is similar to r",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 307,
      "original_number": "307",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 308,
      "original_number": "308",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "S",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/learn/modules/secure-access-azure-identity-services/3-what-is-azure-active-directory\nhttps://docs.microsoft.com/learn/modules/secure-access-azure-identity-services/2-compare-authentication-authorization\nhttps://docs.microsoft.com/learn/modules/secure-access-azure-identity-services/4-what-are-mfa-conditional-access",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 309,
      "original_number": "309",
      "question": "What is guaranteed in an Azure Service Level Agreement (SLA) for virtual machines?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "uptime"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "feature availability"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "bandwidth"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "performance"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nT",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/support/legal/sla/summary/\nhttps://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/support/legal/sla/virtual-machines/v1_9/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 310,
      "original_number": "310",
      "question": "An Azure service is available to all Azure customers when it is in _______",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "public preview"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "private preview"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "development"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "an Enterprise Agreement (EA) subscription"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Public Preview means that the service is in public beta and can be tried out by anyone with an Azure subscription. Services in public preview are\noften offered at a discount price.\nPublic previews are excluded from SLAs and in some cases, no support is offered.\nIncorrect Answers:\nServices in private preview are available only to selected people who has signed up to the private preview program.\n✑ Services in development are not available to the public.\n✑ Services provided under an Enterprise Agreement (EA) subscription are available only to the subscription owner.",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 311,
      "original_number": "311",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYour company plans to purchase an Azure subscription.\nThe company's support policy states that the Azure environment must provide an option to access support engineers by phone or email.\nYou need to recommend which support plan meets the support policy requirement.\nSolution: Recommend a Basic support plan.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nT",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/support/plans/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 312,
      "original_number": "312",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYour company plans to purchase an Azure subscription.\nThe company's support policy states that the Azure environment must provide an option to access support engineers by phone or email.\nYou need to recommend which support plan meets the support policy requirement.\nSolution: Recommend a Standard support plan.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nT",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/support/plans/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 313,
      "original_number": "313",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYour company plans to purchase an Azure subscription.\nThe company's support policy states that the Azure environment must provide an option to access support engineers by phone or email.\nYou need to recommend which support plan meets the support policy requirement.\nSolution: Recommend a Premier support plan.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nT",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/support/plans/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 314,
      "original_number": "314",
      "question": "Your company plans to request an architectural review of an Azure environment from Microsoft.\nThe company currently has a Basic support plan.\nYou need to recommend a new support plan for the company. The solution must minimize costs.\nWhich support plan should you recommend?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Premier"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Developer"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Professional Direct"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Standard"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nT",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/support/plans/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 315,
      "original_number": "315",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "Yes",
        "No",
        "No"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: Yes -\nMost services go to private preview then public preview before being released to general availability.\nThe private preview is only available to certain Azure customers for evaluation purposes. The public preview is available to all Azure customers.\nBox 2: No -\nAzure services in public preview can be managed using the regular management tools: Azure Portal, Azure CLI and PowerShell.\n\nBox 3: No -\nServices in private or public preview are usually offered at reduced costs. However, the costs increase, not decrease when the services are\nreleased to general availability.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Most services go to private preview then public preview before being released to general availability",
        "Azure services in public preview can be managed using the regular management tools: Azure Portal, Azure CLI and PowerShell.",
        "Services in private or public preview are usually offered at reduced costs"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 316,
      "original_number": "316",
      "question": "What is required to use Azure Cost Management?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a Dev/Test subscription"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Software Assurance"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "an Enterprise Agreement (EA)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a pay-as-you-go subscription"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-gb/azure/cost-management/overview-cost-mgt",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 317,
      "original_number": "317",
      "question": "A stopped (deallocated) VM is oline and not mounted on an Azure host server. Starting a VM mounts the VM on a host server before the VM",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Active Directory user accounts so you can continue to create accounts"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Portal"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure host server"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "A stopped (deallocated) VM is oline and not mounted on an Azure host server. Starting a VM mounts the VM on a host server before the VM\nstarts. As soon as the VM is mounted, it becomes chargeable. For this reason, you are unable to start a VM after a trial has expired.\nIncorrect Answers:\n✑ You are not charged for Azure Active Directory user accounts so you can continue to create accounts.\n✑ You can access data that is already stored in Azure.\n✑ You can access the Azure Portal. You can also react",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 318,
      "original_number": "318",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYour company plans to purchase an Azure subscription.\nThe company's support policy states that the Azure environment must provide an option to access support engineers by phone or email.\nYou need to recommend which support plan meets the support policy requirement.\nSolution: Recommend a Professional Direct support plan.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nT",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/support/plans/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 319,
      "original_number": "319",
      "question": "Your company has a Software Assurance agreement that includes Microsoft SQL Server licenses.\nYou plan to deploy SQL Server on Azure virtual machines.\nWhat should you do to minimize licensing costs for the deployment?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Deallocate the virtual machines during off hours."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Use Azure Hybrid Bene+t."
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Con+gure Azure Cost Management budgets."
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Use Azure reservations."
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nA",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/pricing/hybrid-bene+t/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 320,
      "original_number": "320",
      "question": "Your company has 10 departments.\nThe company plans to implement an Azure environment.\nYou need to ensure that each department can use a different payment option for the Azure services it consumes.\nWhat should you create for each department?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a reservation"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "a subscription"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a resource group"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a container instance"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nT",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cost-management-billing/manage/create-subscription",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 321,
      "original_number": "321",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "Yes",
        "No",
        "No"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: Yes -\nAn Azure free account has a spending limit. This is currently 200 USD or 150 GBP.\nBox 2: No -\nAzure free account has a 5 GB blob storage limit and a 5 GB +le storage limit.\nBox 3: No -\nAzure free account has a limit of 10 web, mobile or API apps",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "An Azure free account has a spending limit",
        "Azure free account has a 5 GB blob storage limit and a 5 GB +le storage limit.",
        "Azure free account has a limit of 10 web, mobile or API apps"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 322,
      "original_number": "322",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "Yes",
        "No"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nMost services go to private preview then public preview before being released to general availability. The private preview is only available to\ncertain Azure customers for evaluation purposes.\nBox 2: Yes -\nPublic Preview means that the service is in public beta and can be tried out by anyone with an Azure subscription. Services in public preview are\noften offered at a discount price.\nPublic previews are excluded from SLAs and in some cases, no support is offered.\n\nBox 3: No -\nAn Azure service in general availability is available to all Azure customers, not just a subset of the customers.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Most services go to private preview then public preview before being released to general availability",
        "Public Preview means that the service is in public beta and can be tried out by anyone with an Azure subscription",
        "An Azure service in general availability is available to all Azure customers, not just a subset of the customers."
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 323,
      "original_number": "323",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 324,
      "original_number": "324",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 325,
      "original_number": "325",
      "question": "Composite SLAs involve multiple services supporting an application, each with differing levels of availability. For example, consider an App",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure SQL Database"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure services have the following SLAs"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "Composite SLAs involve multiple services supporting an application, each with differing levels of availability. For example, consider an App\nService web app that writes to Azure SQL Database. At the time of this writing, these Azure services have the following SLAs:\nApp Service web apps = 99.95%\n✑ SQL Database = 99.99%\nWhat is the maximum downtime you would expect for this application? If either service fails, the whole application fails. The probability of each\nservice failing is independent, s",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 326,
      "original_number": "326",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "Yes",
        "Yes",
        "No"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: Yes -\nSLA's vary based on the resource type and the location distribution of the resource. However, the minimum uptime for all Azure services is 99.9\npercent.\nBox 2: Yes -\nThe SLA guaranteed uptime is increased (usually to 99.95 percent) when resources are deployed across multiple regions.\nBox 3: No -\n\nThe number of subscriptions is unrelated to uptime SLA's. You can deploy resources to multiple regions under a single subscription or you can\nhave multiple subscriptions with resources deployed to the same region.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "SLA's vary based on the resource type and the location distribution of the resource",
        "The SLA guaranteed uptime is increased (usually to 99.95 percent) when resources are deployed across multiple regions.",
        "The number of subscriptions is unrelated to uptime SLA's"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 327,
      "original_number": "327",
      "question": "Which statement accurately describes the Modern Lifecycle Policy for Azure services?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Microsoft provides mainstream support for a service for +ve years."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Microsoft provides a minimum of 12 months' notice before ending support for a service."
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "After a service is made generally available, Microsoft provides support for the service for a minimum of four years."
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "When a service is retired, you can purchase extended support for the service for up to +ve years."
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nF",
      "explanation": "https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/30881/modern-lifecycle-policy",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 328,
      "original_number": "328",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nYou need to request that Microsoft increase a subscription quota limit for your company.\nWhich blade should you use from the Azure portal? To answer, select the appropriate blade in the answer area.\n\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-portal/supportability/per-vm-quota-requests",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 329,
      "original_number": "329",
      "question": "Budget alerts notify you when spending, based on usage or cost, reaches or exceeds the amount defined in the alert condition of the budget _______",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Budget alerts notify you when spending, based on usage or cost, reaches or exceeds the amount de+ned in the alert condition of the budget.\nCost Management budgets are created using the Azure portal or the Azure Consumption API.",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 330,
      "original_number": "330",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/support/legal/preview-supplemental-terms/",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 331,
      "original_number": "331",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "Yes",
        "No",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: Yes -\nWith Azure ExpressRoute, all inbound data transfer is free of charge.\nBox 2: No -\nInbound data trahc is free but outbound data trahc is not.\nBox 3: Yes -",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "With Azure ExpressRoute, all inbound data transfer is free of charge.",
        "Inbound data trahc is free but outbound data trahc is not.",
        "Reference:\nhttps://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/pricing/details/expressroute/ https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/pricing/details/bandwidth/"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 332,
      "original_number": "332",
      "question": "Your company has an Azure subscription that contains the following unused resources:\n✑ 20 user accounts in Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)\n✑ Five groups in Azure AD\n✑ 10 public IP addresses\n✑ 10 network interfaces\nYou need to reduce the Azure costs for the company.\nWhich unused resources should you remove?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "the network interfaces"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "the public IP addresses"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "the groups"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "the user accounts"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nY",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/advisor/advisor-cost-recommendations#reduce-costs-by-deleting-or-recon+guring-idle-virtual-\nnetwork-gateways",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 333,
      "original_number": "333",
      "question": "When a virtual machine is stopped (deallocated), the virtual machine is unloaded/dismounted from the physical server in Azure. In this state,",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure and you are charged for the virtual machine itself as well as the"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure portal"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "When a virtual machine is stopped (deallocated), the virtual machine is unloaded/dismounted from the physical server in Azure. In this state,\nyou are not charged for the virtual machine itself. However, you are still charged for the storage costs of the virtual hard disks attached to the\nvirtual machine.\nIf the virtual machine is stopped but not deallocated (this happens if you shut down the virtual machine from the operating system of the virtual\nmachine), the virtual machine is still mounted o",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 334,
      "original_number": "334",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "No",
        "No"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nThe price of Azure storage varies by region. If you use the Azure storage pricing page, you can select different regions and see how the price\nchanges per region.\nBox 2: No -\nYou are charged for read and write operations in general-purpose v2 storage accounts.\nBox 3: No -\nYou would be charge for the read operations of the source storage account and write operations in the destination storage account.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "The price of Azure storage varies by region",
        "You are charged for read and write operations in general-purpose v2 storage accounts.",
        "You would be charge for the read operations of the source storage account and write operations in the destination storage account."
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 335,
      "original_number": "335",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "Yes",
        "No",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: Yes -\nMicrosoft guarantee at least 99.9% availability of the Azure Active Directory Premium edition services. The services are considered available in\nthe following scenarios:\n✑ Users are able to login to the service, login to the Access Panel, access applications on the Access Panel and reset passwords.\n✑ IT administrators are able to create, read, write and delete entries in the directory or provision or de-provision users to applications in the\ndirectory.\nBox 2: No -\nNo SLA is provided for the Free tier of Azure Active Directory.\nBox 3: Yes -\nYou can claim credit if the availability falls below the SLA. The amount of credit depends on the availability. For example: You can claim 25%\ncredit if the availability is less than 99.9%, 50% credit for less than 99% and 100% for less than 95% availability.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Microsoft guarantee at least 99.9% availability of the Azure Active Directory Premium edition services",
        "No SLA is provided for the Free tier of Azure Active Directory.",
        "You can claim credit if the availability falls below the SLA"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 336,
      "original_number": "336",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "No",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nResource groups are logical containers for Azure resources. You do not pay for resource groups.\nBox 2: No -\nData ingress over a VPN is data 'coming in' to Azure over the VPN. You are not charged data transfer costs for data ingress.\nBox 3: Yes -\nData egress over a VPN is data 'going out' of Azure over the VPN. You are charged for data egress.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Resource groups are logical containers for Azure resources",
        "Data ingress over a VPN is data 'coming in' to Azure over the VPN",
        "Data egress over a VPN is data 'going out' of Azure over the VPN"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 337,
      "original_number": "337",
      "question": "Who can use the Azure Total Cost of Ownership (TCO) calculator?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "billing readers for an Azure subscription only"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "owners for an Azure subscription only"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "anyone"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "all users who have an account in Azure Active Directory (Azure AD) that is linked to an Azure subscription only"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nY",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/modules/plan-manage-azure-costs/2-compare-costs-tco-calculator",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 338,
      "original_number": "338",
      "question": "If the SLA for an Azure service is not met, you receive a credit that can be applied to your bill _______",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "If the SLA for an Azure service is not met, you receive credits for that service and that service only. The credits are deducted from your monthly\nbill for that service.\nIf you stopped using the service where the SLA was not met, your account would remain in credit for that service. The credits would not be\napplied to any other services that you may be using.\nService Credits apply only to fees paid for the particular Service, Service Resource, or Service tier for which a Service Level has not been met. In\ncases where\nService Levels apply to individual Service Resources or to separate Service tiers, Service Credits apply only to fees paid for the affected Service\nResource or\nService tier, as applicable. The Service Credits awarded in any billing month for a particular Service or Service Res",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 339,
      "original_number": "339",
      "question": "Which task can you perform by using Azure Advisor?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Integrate Active Directory and Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Estimate the costs of an Azure solution."
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Con+rm that Azure subscription security follows best practices."
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Evaluate which on-premises resources can be migrated to Azure."
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nR",
      "explanation": "https://blog.pragmaticworks.com/what-is-azure-advi-\nsor#:~:text=Microsoft%20de+nes%20Azure%20Advisor%20as,solutions%20based%20on%20that%20data",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 340,
      "original_number": "340",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "Yes",
        "No"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nAzure Free Account gives you 12 months access to the most popular free services. It also gives you a credit (150 GBP or 200 USD) to use on\nany Azure service for up to 30 days.\nBox 2: Yes -\nAll free accounts expire after 12 months.\nBox 3: No -\nYou can only create one free Azure account per Microsoft account.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Azure Free Account gives you 12 months access to the most popular free services",
        "All free accounts expire after 12 months.",
        "You can only create one free Azure account per Microsoft account."
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 341,
      "original_number": "341",
      "question": "You have an Azure application that uses the services shown in the following table.\nHow should you calculate the composite SLA for the application?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "0.999 * 0.9999 = 0.9989001 = 99.89001%"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "0.999 / 0.9999 = 0.9991 = 99.91%"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Max(0.999, 0.9999) = 0.9999 = 99.99%"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Min(0.999, 0.9999) = 0.999 = 99.9%"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nC",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/architecture/reliability/requirements#understand-service-level-agreements",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 342,
      "original_number": "342",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/shows/azure-videos/virtual-spot-machines-overview",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 343,
      "original_number": "343",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/advisor/advisor-cost-recommendations https://build5nines.com/properly-shutdown-azure-vm-to-save-\nmoney/",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 344,
      "original_number": "344",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "P",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/support/legal/preview-supplemental-terms https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/overview/what-is-saas/",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 345,
      "original_number": "345",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://www.parkmycloud.com/does-azure-charge-for-stopped-vm/",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 346,
      "original_number": "346",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/privacystatement",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 347,
      "original_number": "347",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "B",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-365/compliance/compliance-manager-setup",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 348,
      "original_number": "348",
      "question": "You have 1,000 virtual machines hosted on the Hyper-V hosts in a data center.\nYou plan to migrate all the virtual machines to an Azure pay-as-you-go subscription.\nYou need to identify which expenditure model to use for the planned Azure solution.\nWhich expenditure model should you identify?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "scalable"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "operational"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "elastic"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "capital"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nO",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/architecture/cloud-adoption/appendix/azure-scaffold",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 349,
      "original_number": "349",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 350,
      "original_number": "350",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 351,
      "original_number": "351",
      "question": "Which Service Level Agreement (SLA) is provided for Azure services in public preview?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Each service de+nes its own SLA"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "The SLA will be 99%"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "The SLA will be 1% less than the general availability (GA) SLA"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "The SLA will be 99.95%"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 352,
      "original_number": "352",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 353,
      "original_number": "353",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "Yes",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nWithin most of the areas, there are clearly more expensive regions and less expensive regions.\nThe least expensive regions, on average across these instance types are us-west-2, us-west-central, and korea-south.\nThe most expensive regions are asia-paci+c-east, japan-east, and australia-east.\nBox 2: Yes -\nMany organizations with Microsoft Enterprise Agreements (EA) are adding Azure to their EA to enjoy the bene+ts it offers, such as:\nMinimizing Azure upfront costs by locking in pricing with consumption pre-commitment\nUsing Azure EA Portal to manage Azure Subscriptions easily and organize them under a single billing account\nBox 3: Yes -",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Within most of the areas, there are clearly more expensive regions and less expensive regions",
        "Many organizations with Microsoft Enterprise Agreements (EA) are adding Azure to their EA to enjoy the bene+ts it offers, such as:\nMinimizing Azure upfront costs by locking in pricing with consumption",
        "Reference:\nhttps://www.parkmycloud.com/blog/azure-region-pricing/\nhttps://blog.turbonomic.com/introducing-microsoft-azure-enterprise-agreement-ea-support-in-turbonomic-6.4"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 354,
      "original_number": "354",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "Yes",
        "No",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: Yes -\nThe Pay as You Go model is billed on a per second basis and you can start or stop the service at any time ג€\" paying only for what you use.\nBox 2: No -\nNo, it is OpEx (Operational Expenditures).\nOpEx: The business can achieve ROI immediately in many cases because the infrastructure is managed by the cloud provider.\nCapEx: ROI is not usually realized until a long time after the purchase was made because the infrastructure needs to be set up and employees\nneed to be trained.\nComputers, servers, and other hardware needed for on-premises data centers are all examples of CapEx.\nBox 3: Yes -\nOperational Expenditures (OpEx) are the ongoing costs related to day-to-day operations. A subscription fee for cloud services is considered\nOpExג€\"the cloud provider is making the infrastructure investment upfront, and you only pay for the resources you need as you need them.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "The Pay as You Go model is billed on a per second basis and you can start or stop the service at any time ג€\" paying only for what you use.",
        "No, it is OpEx (Operational Expenditures)",
        "Operational Expenditures (OpEx) are the ongoing costs related to day-to-day operations"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 355,
      "original_number": "355",
      "question": "What is the longest term you can purchase for Azure Reserved VM instances?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "one year"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "+ve years"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "four years"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "three years"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nA",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cost-management-billing/reservations/save-compute-costs-reservations",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 356,
      "original_number": "356",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "Yes",
        "No"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nServices in private preview can be viewed in the regular Azure portal. However, you need to be signed up for the feature in private preview\nbefore you can view it.\nAccess to private preview features is usually by invitation only.\nBox 2: Yes -\nYou can use services in public preview in production environments. However, you should be aware that the service may have faults, is not\nsubject to an SLA and may be withdrawn without notice.\nBox 3: No -\nPublic previews are excluded from SLAs and in some cases, no support is offered.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Services in private preview can be viewed in the regular Azure portal",
        "You can use services in public preview in production environments",
        "Public previews are excluded from SLAs and in some cases, no support is offered."
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 357,
      "original_number": "357",
      "question": "Your company has 10 ohces. You plan to generate several billing reports from the Azure portal. Each report will contain the Azure resource\nutilization of each ohce.\nWhich Azure Resource Manager feature should you use before you generate the reports?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "tags"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "templates"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "locks"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "policies"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nY",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/cloud-adoption-framework/decision-guides/resource-tagging/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 358,
      "original_number": "358",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "Yes",
        "No"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nAn Azure free account comes with a 'basic' support plan, not a 'standard' support plan.\nBox 2: Yes -\nYou can purchase the Professional Direct, Standard, and Developer support plans with the Microsoft Customer Agreement. You can also\npurchase the\nProfessional and Standard support plans with the Enterprise Agreement.\nBox 3: No -\nUsers with any type of Azure subscription (pay-as-you-go, Enterprise Agreement, Microsoft Customer Agreement etc.) can get support from the\nMSDN forums.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "An Azure free account comes with a 'basic' support plan, not a 'standard' support plan.",
        "You can purchase the Professional Direct, Standard, and Developer support plans with the Microsoft Customer Agreement",
        "Users with any type of Azure subscription (pay-as-you-go, Enterprise Agreement, Microsoft Customer Agreement etc.) can get support from the\nMSDN forums."
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 359,
      "original_number": "359",
      "question": "This question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.\nIf Microsoft plans to end support for an Azure service that does NOT have a successor service, Microsoft will provide noti+cation at least 12\nmonths before.\nInstructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed`. If the statement is incorrect, select the\nanswer choice that makes the statement correct.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "No change is needed."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "6 months"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "90 days"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "30 days"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nT",
      "explanation": "https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/30881",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 360,
      "original_number": "360",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "Yes",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nYou need to be an administrator of the billing account that has the subscription to be able to transfer the subscription. This could be a Billing\nAdministrator or\nGlobal Administrator. A subscription owner can manage all resources and permissions within the subscription but cannot transfer ownership of\nthe subscription.\nBox 2: Yes -\nYou can convert a free trial subscription to Pay-As-You-Go. This is common practice for people who wish to continue using the Azure services\nwhen the free trial period expires.\nBox 3: Yes -\nYou can remove the spending limit, but you can't increase or decrease it.\nThe spending limit in Azure prevents spending over your credit amount. All new customers who sign up for an Azure free account or\nsubscription types that include credits over multiple months have the spending limit turned on by default. The spending limit is equal to the\namount of credit and it can't be changed. For example, if you signed up for Azure free account, your spending limit i",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "You need to be an administrator of the billing account that has the subscription to be able to transfer the subscription",
        "You can convert a free trial subscription to Pay-As-You-Go",
        "You can remove the spending limit, but you can't increase or decrease it"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 361,
      "original_number": "361",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "Yes",
        "No",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: Yes -\nA reservation is where you commit to pay for a resource (for example a virtual machine) for one or three years. This gives you a discounted\nprice on the resource for the reservation period.\nBox 2: No -\nThere are other factors that injuence the cost of a virtual machine such as the virtual hard disks attached to the virtual machine. You could\nhave multiple virtual machines with the same 'size' (B2S in this case) but with different virtual hard disk con+gurations.\nBox 3: Yes -\nWhen a virtual machine is stopped (deallocated), the virtual machine is unloaded/dismounted from the physical server in Azure. In this state,\nyou are not charged for the virtual machine itself. However, you are still charged for the storage costs of the virtual hard disks attached to the\nvirtual machine.\nIf the virtual machine is stopped but not deallocated (this happens if you shut down the virtual machine from the operating system of the virtual\nmachine), the virtual machine is still mounted on the p",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "A reservation is where you commit to pay for a resource (for example a virtual machine) for one or three years",
        "There are other factors that injuence the cost of a virtual machine such as the virtual hard disks attached to the virtual machine",
        "When a virtual machine is stopped (deallocated), the virtual machine is unloaded/dismounted from the physical server in Azure"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 362,
      "original_number": "362",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYour company has an Azure subscription that contains the following unused resources:\n✑ 20 user accounts in Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)\n✑ Five groups in Azure AD\n✑ 10 public IP addresses\n✑ 10 network interfaces\nYou need to reduce the Azure costs for the company.\nSolution: You remove the unused network interfaces.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nY",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/advisor/advisor-cost-recommendations#reduce-costs-by-deleting-or-recon+guring-idle-virtual-\nnetwork-gateways",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 363,
      "original_number": "363",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYour company has an Azure subscription that contains the following unused resources:\n✑ 20 user accounts in Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)\nFive groups in Azure AD -\n✑ 10 public IP addresses\n✑ 10 network interfaces\nYou need to reduce the Azure costs for the company.\nSolution: You remove the unused public IP addresses.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nY",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/advisor/advisor-cost-recommendations#reduce-costs-by-deleting-or-recon+guring-idle-virtual-\nnetwork-gateways",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 364,
      "original_number": "364",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYour company has an Azure subscription that contains the following unused resources:\n✑ 20 user accounts in Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)\n✑ Five groups in Azure AD\n✑ 10 public IP addresses\n✑ 10 network interfaces\nYou need to reduce the Azure costs for the company.\nSolution: You remove the unused user accounts.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nY",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/advisor/advisor-cost-recommendations#reduce-costs-by-deleting-or-recon+guring-idle-virtual-\nnetwork-gateways",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 365,
      "original_number": "365",
      "question": "How should you calculate the monthly uptime percentage?\n\nFormula: A ÷ B × C\n\nTo answer, select the appropriate options for A, B, and C.\n\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "\"",
      "explanation": "Monthly Uptime % = (Maximum Available Minutes - Downtime in Minutes) / Maximum Available Minutes × 100\n\nA = (Maximum Available Minutes - Downtime in Minutes)\nB = Maximum Available Minutes\nC = 100",
      "questionType": "MATCHING",
      "matchingItems": [
        {
          "item": "A",
          "options": [
            "Downtime in Minutes",
            "Maximum Available Minutes",
            "(Maximum Available Minutes - Downtime in Minutes)"
          ],
          "answer": "(Maximum Available Minutes - Downtime in Minutes)"
        },
        {
          "item": "B",
          "options": [
            "60",
            "1,440",
            "Maximum Available Minutes"
          ],
          "answer": "Maximum Available Minutes"
        },
        {
          "item": "C",
          "options": [
            "100",
            "99.99",
            "1.440"
          ],
          "answer": "100"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 366,
      "original_number": "366",
      "question": "For each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": [
        "No",
        "No",
        "Yes"
      ],
      "explanation": "Box 1: No -\nResource groups are logical containers for Azure resources. You do not pay for resource groups.\nBox 2: No -\nData ingress over a VPN is data 'coming in' to Azure over the VPN. You are not charged data transfer costs for data ingress.\nBox 3: Yes -\nData egress over a VPN is data 'going out' of Azure over the VPN. You are charged for data egress.",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT",
      "statements": [
        "Resource groups are logical containers for Azure resources",
        "Data ingress over a VPN is data 'coming in' to Azure over the VPN",
        "Data egress over a VPN is data 'going out' of Azure over the VPN"
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 367,
      "original_number": "367",
      "question": "This question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.\nA support plan solution that gives you best practice information, health status and noti+cations, and 24/7 access to billing information at the\nlowest possible cost is a Standard support plan.\nInstructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed`. If the statement is incorrect, select the\nanswer choice that makes the statement correct.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "No change is needed"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Developer"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Basic"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Premier"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nA",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/support/plans/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 368,
      "original_number": "368",
      "question": "In which Azure support plans can you open a new support request?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Premier and Professional Direct only"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Premier, Professional Direct, and Standard only"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Premier, Professional Direct, Standard, and Developer only"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Premier, Professional Direct, Standard, Developer, and Basic"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nY",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/support/plans/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 369,
      "original_number": "369",
      "question": "This question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.\nYou can create an Azure support request from support.microsoft.com.\nInstructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed.` If the statement is incorrect, select the\nanswer choice that makes the statement correct.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "No change is needed."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "the Azure portal"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "the Knowledge Center"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "the Security & Compliance admin center"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nY",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/azure-supportability/how-to-create-azure-support-request",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 370,
      "original_number": "370",
      "question": "Note: This question is part of a series of questions that present the same scenario. Each question in the series contains a unique solution that\nmight meet the stated goals. Some question sets might have more than one correct solution, while others might not have a correct solution.\nAfter you answer a question in this section, you will NOT be able to return to it. As a result, these questions will not appear in the review screen.\nYour company has an Azure subscription that contains the following unused resources:\n✑ 20 user accounts in Azure Active Directory (Azure AD)\n✑ Five groups in Azure AD\n✑ 10 public IP addresses\n✑ 10 network interfaces\nYou need to reduce the Azure costs for the company.\nSolution: You remove the unused groups.\nDoes this meet the goal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Yes"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "No"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nY",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/azure/advisor/advisor-cost-recommendations#reduce-costs-by-deleting-or-recon+guring-idle-virtual-\nnetwork-gateways",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 371,
      "original_number": "371",
      "question": "This question requires that you evaluate the underlined text to determine if it is correct.\nThe Azure Standard support plan is the lowest cost option to receive 24x7 access to support engineers by phone.\nInstructions: Review the underlined text. If it makes the statement correct, select `No change is needed`. If the statement is incorrect, select the\nanswer choice that makes the statement correct.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "No change is needed"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Developer"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Basic"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Professional Direct"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nT",
      "explanation": "https://azure.microsoft.com/en-gb/support/plans/",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 372,
      "original_number": "372",
      "question": "All Azure services that are in public preview are _______",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "provided without any documentation"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "only configurable from Azure CLI"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "excluded from the Service Level Agreements"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "only configurable from the Azure portal"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C",
      "explanation": "Preview features are made available to you on the condition that you accept additional terms which supplement the regular Azure terms. The\nsupplemental terms state:\nPREVIEWS ARE PROVIDED \"AS-IS,\" \"WITH ALL FAULTS,\" AND \"AS AVAILABLE,\" AND ARE EXCLUDED FROM THE SERVICE LEVEL AGREEMENTS\nAND\nLIMITED WARRANTY.",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 373,
      "original_number": "373",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "R",
      "explanation": "https://docs.microsoft.com/en-us/learn/modules/plan-manage-azure-costs/2-compare-costs-tco-calculator",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 374,
      "original_number": "374",
      "question": "You need to compare a company's cloud usage to industry standard best practices.\nWhat should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Monitor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Service Health"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Application Insights in Azure Monitor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Advisor"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 375,
      "original_number": "375",
      "question": "You need to start Azure Cloud Shell.\nWhat should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "the Azure portal"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Command-Line Interface (CLI)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure PowerShell"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "an Azure Resource Manager (ARM) template"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 376,
      "original_number": "376",
      "question": "How many copies of data are maintained by an Azure Storage account that uses locally-redundant storage (LRS)?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "3"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "4"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "6"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "9"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 377,
      "original_number": "377",
      "question": "What enables a cloud service to adapt quickly to changing requirements?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "high availability"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "predictability"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "manageability"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "agility"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 378,
      "original_number": "378",
      "question": "What is an example of vertical scaling in a cloud environment?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "adding an additional CPU to an existing Azure virtual machine"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "adding an additional Azure virtual machine"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "adding an additional Azure Virtual Desktop session host"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "adding an additional Azure App Service instance automatically"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 379,
      "original_number": "379",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 380,
      "original_number": "380",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 381,
      "original_number": "381",
      "question": "What additional resource is required by an Azure virtual machine?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a virtual network"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "a service endpoint"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Firewall"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a public IP address"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 382,
      "original_number": "382",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 383,
      "original_number": "383",
      "question": "How many copies of data are maintained by an Azure Storage account that uses geo-redundant storage (GRS)?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "3"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "4"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "6"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "9"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 384,
      "original_number": "384",
      "question": "What is used to grant permission to Azure Virtual Desktop resources?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "tags"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "role-based access control (RBAC) roles"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "resource groups"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "application security groups"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 385,
      "original_number": "385",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.\n:",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOT_AREA"
    },
    {
      "id": 386,
      "original_number": "386",
      "question": "Match the cloud computing bene+ts to the appropriate requirements.\nTo answer, drag the appropriate bene+t from the column on the left to its requirement on the right. Each bene+t may be used once, more than\nonce, or not at all.\nNOTE: Each correct match is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 387,
      "original_number": "387",
      "question": "Match the Azure services to the appropriate descriptions.\nTo answer, drag the appropriate service from the column on the left to its description on the right. Each service may be used once, more than\nonce, or not at all.\nNOTE: Each correct match is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 388,
      "original_number": "388",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 389,
      "original_number": "389",
      "question": "Which cloud service model minimizes the management responsibility of a customer?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "infrastructure as a service (IaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "platform as a service (PaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "software as a service (SaaS)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 390,
      "original_number": "390",
      "question": "You need to identify a customer’s level of shared responsibility based on the cloud service model.\nIn which order should you list each model from most customer responsibility to least customer responsibility? To answer, move all models from\nthe list of models to the answer area and arrange them in the correct order.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 391,
      "original_number": "391",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 392,
      "original_number": "392",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 393,
      "original_number": "393",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 394,
      "original_number": "394",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 395,
      "original_number": "395",
      "question": "Match the Azure storage services to the appropriate descriptions.\nTo answer, drag the appropriate storage service from the column on the left to its description on the right. Each service may be used once, more\nthan once, or not at all.\nNOTE: Each correct match is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 396,
      "original_number": "396",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 397,
      "original_number": "397",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 398,
      "original_number": "398",
      "question": "You have an Azure web app.\nYou need to manage the settings of the web app from an iPhone.\nWhat are two Azure management tools that you can use? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Windows PowerShell"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Cloud Shell"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "the Azure portal"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Storage Explorer"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "BC\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 399,
      "original_number": "399",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nYou need to create a new Azure +le share.\nWhat should you use? To answer, select the service in the answer area.\n\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 400,
      "original_number": "400",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 401,
      "original_number": "401",
      "question": "What should you use to prevent trahc from an Azure virtual network from being routed to an Azure Storage account via the internet?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a network security group (NSG)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "a public endpoint"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure VPN Gateway"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a service endpoint"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 402,
      "original_number": "402",
      "question": "Which service can replace a resource lock automatically if the lock is removed?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Information Protection (AIP)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Blueprints"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Backup"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Advisor"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 403,
      "original_number": "403",
      "question": "You need to create a _______ new user for an Azure subscription.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Option A - See explanation"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Option B - See explanation"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Option C - See explanation"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Option D - See explanation"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 404,
      "original_number": "404",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 405,
      "original_number": "405",
      "question": "You plan to collect and analyze event details for +ve Azure virtual machines.\nYou need to run queries to compare the event details collected from all the virtual machines.\nWhich two tools should you use? Each correct answer presents part of the solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Service Health"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Service Bus"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Monitor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Advisor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "Log Analytics"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "CE\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 406,
      "original_number": "406",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 407,
      "original_number": "407",
      "question": "What should you use to track the costs of Azure resources?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Quickstart templates"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "tags"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "budgets"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "usage and quotas"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 408,
      "original_number": "408",
      "question": "You have an Azure subscription.\nYou plan to create a virtual machine.\nWhere will the virtual machine be placed in Azure?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "In a storage account"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "In a resource group"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "In an administrative unit"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "In an application group"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 409,
      "original_number": "409",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 410,
      "original_number": "410",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 411,
      "original_number": "411",
      "question": "You plan to reduce ongoing Azure expenditures.\nYou need to identify which factors affect the costs of a resource.\nWhich three factors should you identify? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "the volume of outbound data"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "the volume of inbound data"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "the service tier"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "the Azure region"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "the type of processed data"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "ACE\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 412,
      "original_number": "412",
      "question": "Your company has an Azure subscription that contains several resources.\nYou need to identify which department is responsible for the cost of each resource.\nWhat should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "budgets"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "alerts"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "tags"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 413,
      "original_number": "413",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 414,
      "original_number": "414",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 415,
      "original_number": "415",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 416,
      "original_number": "416",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 417,
      "original_number": "417",
      "question": "HOTSPOT -\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 418,
      "original_number": "418",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 419,
      "original_number": "419",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 420,
      "original_number": "420",
      "question": "You have on-premises servers that run Windows Server.\nWhat should you implement to manage the servers by using the Azure portal?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Arc"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Docker"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "role-based access control (RBAC)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 421,
      "original_number": "421",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 422,
      "original_number": "422",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 423,
      "original_number": "423",
      "question": "You have a web app that runs in Azure.\nYou need to identify the amount of time it takes for web pages to load in a user's browser.\nWhat should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Monitor alerts"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Application Insights in Azure Monitor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Log Analytics"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Network Watcher"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 424,
      "original_number": "424",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 425,
      "original_number": "425",
      "question": "What should a desktop application use to interact with Azure and manage resources?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "APIs"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Resource Manager (ARM) templates"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Command-Line Interface (CLI)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Cloud Shell"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 426,
      "original_number": "426",
      "question": "Match the cloud computing bene+ts to the appropriate requirements.\nTo answer, drag the appropriate bene+t from the column on the left to its requirement on the right. Each bene+t may be used once, more than\nonce, or not at all.\nNOTE: Each correct match is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 427,
      "original_number": "427",
      "question": "Match the security components to the appropriate defense in depth layers.\nTo answer, drag the appropriate security component from the column on the left to its defense in depth layer on the right Each security component\nmay be used once, more than once, or not at all.\nNOTE: Each correct match is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 428,
      "original_number": "428",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 429,
      "original_number": "429",
      "question": "Which two features or services can be integrated with Azure Monitor? Each correct answer presents part of the solution.\nNOTE: Each correct answer is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure status"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Application Insights"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Advisor"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Log Analytics"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "Azure Service Health"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "BD\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 430,
      "original_number": "430",
      "question": "What provides a uni+ed way to project and manage non-Azure resources in Azure Resource Manager (ARM)?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Migrate"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure AD Connect"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure Arc"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Front Door"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "C\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 431,
      "original_number": "431",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 432,
      "original_number": "432",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 433,
      "original_number": "433",
      "question": "Your company has an Azure subscription and three business units.\nYou plan to deploy new resources for each business unit.\nYou need to ensure that the new resources are deployed by using a repeatable and reliable method that applies the same con+gurations to each\nresource.\nWhat should you use?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Policy"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Arc"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a resource group"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Azure Resource Manager (ARM) templates"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 434,
      "original_number": "434",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 435,
      "original_number": "435",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 436,
      "original_number": "436",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 437,
      "original_number": "437",
      "question": "In the software as a service (SaaS) cloud service, which responsibility is shared between Microsoft and the customer?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "identity and directory infrastructure management"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "application management"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "information and data management"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "operating system updates"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 438,
      "original_number": "438",
      "question": "Where does Azure Monitor store event data?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "an Azure Blob Storage account"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Azure Storage Queue"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Azure SQL Database"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a Log Analytics workspace"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 439,
      "original_number": "439",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 440,
      "original_number": "440",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 441,
      "original_number": "441",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 442,
      "original_number": "442",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 443,
      "original_number": "443",
      "question": "An Azure administrator plans to run a PowerShell script that creates Azure resources.\nYou need to recommend which computer con+guration to use to run the script.\nWhich three computers can run the script? Each correct answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "a computer that runs Windows 11 and has the Azure CLI tools installed"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "a computer that runs Linux and has the Azure CLI tools installed"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a computer that runs macOS and has PowerShell Core 6.0 installed"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a computer that runs Chrome OS and uses Azure Cloud Shell"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "a computer that runs Windows 10 and has the Azure PowerShell module installed"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "CDE\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 444,
      "original_number": "444",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 445,
      "original_number": "445",
      "question": "In the infrastructure as a service (IaaS) cloud service model, which two components are the responsibility of the cloud service provider? Each\ncorrect answer presents a complete solution.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "the con+guration and maintenance of storage"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "the installation and con+guration of the operating system"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "maintaining the hardware"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "the network con+guration"
        },
        {
          "letter": "E",
          "text": "physical security of the datacenter infrastructure"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "CE\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 446,
      "original_number": "446",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 447,
      "original_number": "447",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 448,
      "original_number": "448",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 449,
      "original_number": "449",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 450,
      "original_number": "450",
      "question": "You have an Azure Storage account named storage1.\nYou need to ensure that containers can be created in, but not deleted from, storage1.\nWhat should you do?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Create a ReadOnly lock for storage1."
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Create a delete lock for storage1."
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "Enable container soft delete."
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "Enable blob soft delete."
        }
      ],
      "answer": "B\nC",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 451,
      "original_number": "451",
      "question": "You have an Azure subscription.\nYou need to use Azure Cloud Shell to run a deployment script.\nWhat should you use to access Cloud Shell?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "Azure Resource Manager (ARM)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "Microsoft Visual Studio"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "a Windows command prompt"
        },
        {
          "letter": "D",
          "text": "a web browser"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "D\nT",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 452,
      "original_number": "452",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 453,
      "original_number": "453",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 454,
      "original_number": "454",
      "question": "You need to migrate an on-premises server by using a lift-and-shift migration.\nTo which type of cloud service should you migrate?",
      "options": [
        {
          "letter": "A",
          "text": "infrastructure as a service (IaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "B",
          "text": "software as a service (SaaS)"
        },
        {
          "letter": "C",
          "text": "platform as a service (PaaS)"
        }
      ],
      "answer": "A\n\nT",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "MULTIPLE_CHOICE"
    },
    {
      "id": 455,
      "original_number": "455",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 456,
      "original_number": "456",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nSelect the answer that correctly completes the sentence.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 457,
      "original_number": "457",
      "question": "Match the Azure compute services to the appropriate descriptions.\nTo answer, drag the appropriate compute service from the column on the left to its description on the right. Each service may be used once, more\nthan once, or not at all.\nNOTE: Each correct match is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "DRAG_DROP"
    },
    {
      "id": 458,
      "original_number": "458",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "T",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    },
    {
      "id": 459,
      "original_number": "459",
      "question": "HOTSPOT\n-\nFor each of the following statements, select Yes if the statement is true. Otherwise, select No.\nNOTE: Each correct selection is worth one point.",
      "options": [],
      "answer": "",
      "explanation": "",
      "questionType": "HOTSPOT"
    }
  ]
}